<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns2:topic xmlns:ns2="http://schema/" topicid="1368821">
    <topicname>Asia</topicname>
    <news newsid="1370048">
        <title>Witnesses describe terrifying scene at deadly Shanghai New Year's stampede</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/china-shanghai-new-years-stampede/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Shanghai police rule out rush for "dollar coupons" as cause of stampede</highlights>
        <highlights>"I was surrounded by the sounds of girls crying and shouting for help," one man says</highlights>
        <highlights>Thirty-six people are killed, 47 injured, government says; Many victims reportedly students</highlights>
        <highlights>Witness tells of efforts to carry people who'd fainted to safety, resuscitate others</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T15:31:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Jethro Mullen and Laura Smith-Spark, CNN</author>
        <content>Hong Kong (CNN) -- Zuo Zhijian says the heavy crush of bodies around him on the Shanghai waterfront left him unable to move his legs."I also had someone grabbing my hair from the back, struggling and breathing heavily," Zuo said. "A girl in front of me held me desperately and said, 'Help me, help me, please. I can't make it anymore.' There was also a girl completely motionless underneath."Zuo was one among many people caught up in the stampede on the Bund, an area along the Huangpu River in China's most populous city that draws big crowds for New Year's Eve festivities. He described his traumatic experience on Weibo, a Chinese social media platform on which he's a verified user.The stampede, which began roughly 25 minutes before midnight, killed 36 people and injured 47 others, the Shanghai city government said. Many of the victims were female students, state media reported.'Girls crying and shouting for help'"I was surrounded by the sounds of girls crying and shouting for help with their last strain of effort, and of people fighting and throwing curses at each other," said Zuo, who works in the media sector.Another witness, 28-year-old Tian Ye, who works in import-export logistics, told CNN how he'd gone down to the waterfront to enjoy the festivities because he lives nearby.Instead, he found himself only about 30 meters (about 100 feet) from the scene of the deadly crush."When me and other young men saw people had fainted, we rushed there to do CPR and carried them to the ambulance and police cars," he said.The stampede lasted only about 30 seconds, he said, but it took about 10 minutes to carry everyone out."There were way too many people stuck down there without a clear entrance or exit; people got stuck and panicked. A lot of police gathered in that central area, but more police could have eased the consequences," he said."When someone fell down, people behind would think the crowd is moving, so more people were moving forward and falling."He blamed what happened on overcrowding, people's lack of awareness of how to protect themselves, and on heavy traffic that blocked ambulances from getting to the scene sooner."But I'm happy to see everyone around me fighting to help others after the tragedy," he added."No conspiracy, no predesign, it's a tragedy triggered by multiple factors. We tried our best, wish them rest in peace."Unconscious victimsA third witness, Xiao Ji, said he was at the side of the mass of people as a night of celebration turned into scenes of horror."I stared for a while and then started pulling people out of the crowds," Xiao, who works at a technology company, said on Weibo. Exhausted after hauling two people out of the crush, he said all he could do was "hold their hands and try to cheer them up a little bit."In the chaos described by Xiao, some people were trying to revive unconscious victims and others were simply wailing. Police officers were also trying to help. After he regained strength, Xiao says, he joined in again.A photo from China's state-run news agency Xinhua showed people receiving treatment as they lay in the middle of a crowded street.Cause under investigationThe terrifying crush left a grisly aftermath."People lying on the ground were a complete mess," said Zuo. "Their faces became unrecognizable."It remains unclear what caused the stampede. Authorities are investigating what happened.Xinhua cited one unidentified witness as saying that people started scrambling after coupons that looked like dollar bills were thrown from the third floor of a building.But the Shanghai police said their investigation had ruled out this possibility.Police said that based on surveillance camera footage, the items were tossed about 10 minutes after the stampede and did not cause much commotion. They were coupons from a bar on the Bund.Zuo, Xiao, Tian and other witnesses also made no mention of the coupons in their accounts. And the English-language newspaper Shanghai Daily cited witnesses as saying that the stampede started "when a large number of people trying to move up to the riverfront esplanade were blocked."CNN reached out to Zuo and Xiao for further comment, but Zuo didn't immediately respond and Xiao declined to talk to the media.Event moved after problemsLocal officials had this year moved a popular New Year's Eve light show from an open area of the Bund to a more enclosed area, citing safety concerns, Shanghai Daily reported."Last year, officials were caught off-guard when nearly 300,000 people turned up for the New Year countdown at the Bund, which led to traffic chaos," the newspaper said.Officials canceled another New Year's celebration late Wednesday in front of Beijing's tallest skyscraper, citing safety concerns.Even with the light show and official countdown called off, many revelers remained at the location and had their own countdown there.Flowers laid at the sceneThe Shanghai stampede prompted scenes of anger and grief.Video from the Reuters news agency showed people sobbing in a hospital waiting room. One woman told state broadcaster CCTV that relatives had been waiting for hours for information about their loved ones.A photo from Agence France-Presse showed people facing off with security guards at a hospital.Dozens of people gathered at the scene of the stampede Thursday, laying bouquets of flowers on the ground. Police cars lined an intersection near where the deadly chaos took place.Chinese President Xi Jinping requested "an immediate investigation" into what happened and said "a profound lesson should be learned" from the events, Xinhua reported Thursday.Zuo spelled out what he learned from the terrible end to 2014: Don't attend big gatherings like that ever again.CNN's Jethro Mullen reported and wrote in Hong Kong and Laura Smith-Spark wrote in London. CNN's Steven Jiang, Serena Dong, Yuli Yang, CY Xu and Catherine E. Shoichet contributed to this report. Journalist Connie Young also contributed.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072233-01-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072336-02-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072435-03-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072535-04-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072805-05-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072859-06-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072233-01-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072336-02-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072435-03-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072535-04-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072805-05-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072859-06-shanghai-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101072233-01-shanghai-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231183707-lok-ripley-china-beijing-nye-celebration-canceled-00004329-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185841im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1371891">
        <title>Stampede at Shanghai New Year's celebration kills 35</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/asia/china-shanghai-new-years-stampede/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Witness tells Xinhua people were scrambling for dollar-shaped coupons</highlights>
        <highlights>Stampede breaks out at a New Year's celebration in Shanghai</highlights>
        <highlights>At least 35 people are killed, state media report; authorities are investigating</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T04:11:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Steven Jiang and Catherine E. Shoichet, CNN</author>
        <content>Beijing (CNN) -- New Year's festivities in China's most populous city were cut short Wednesday after a stampede left at least 35 people dead and dozens injured.Posts on Twitter and China's Weibo social network described a chaotic scene and rescue efforts along the Shanghai riverfront.Photos showed large crowds packing a street near the river and emergency medical workers treating people on the ground.The stampede broke out around 11:35 p.m. Wednesday along the city's riverfront, the state-run Xinhua news agency said. At least 42 people were injured, Xinhua reported.Authorities are investigating the cause, Xinhua said.A witness told the government-run news agency that people started scrambling after coupons that looked like dollar bills were thrown from the third floor of a building.Many of the dead were young students, CCTV America reported, citing Shanghai rescue authorities.Video from the Reuters news agency showed people sobbing in a hospital waiting room. One woman told CCTV they'd been waiting for hours for information about their loved ones.The promenade in the area known as the Bund along the Huangpu River is a popular spot for New Year's Eve festivities in Shanghai.But last week, Shanghai Daily reported that local officials had called off a popular New Year's Eve light show there, citing police concerns over crowd control. Last year, the event drew nearly 300,000 people and "dispersing the crowd became a massive administrative headache," the newspaper said.Scaled-back celebrations had been planned in several parts of the city instead, according to the newspaper.Officials canceled another New Year's celebration late Wednesday in front of Beijing's tallest skyscraper, citing safety concerns.Even with the light show and official countdown called off, many revelers remained at the location and had their own countdown there.CNN's Steven Jiang reported from Beijing. CNN's Catherine E. Shoichet wrote the story in Atlanta. CNN's Anna-Maja Rappard contributed</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231183707-lok-ripley-china-beijing-nye-celebration-canceled-00004329-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185842im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1373427">
        <title>Dignity in tragedy: Missing AirAsia captain's family remember loving father</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/indonesia-airasia-iranto-tuchman/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>CNN crew speaks to the family of the captain of AirAsia Flight QZ8501</highlights>
        <highlights>Irianto was a highly-experienced former air force pilot</highlights>
        <highlights>Pilot's wife describes him as a kind and loving man who was hard-working and dedicated</highlights>
        <highlights>Daughter holds out hope that he and other passengers may have survived</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T07:13:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Gary Tuchman, CNN</author>
        <content>Surabaya, Indonesia (CNN) -- The man who captained AirAsia Flight QZ8501 lived in a picturesque neighborhood in the suburbs of Surabaya, Indonesia's second-largest city.We headed there to see if family members or friends wanted to talk to us about him. These types of assignments are never easy. We are well aware that the last thing many people in mourning want to do is to talk to a journalist. I've done this long enough to know that the smart thing is to have the decency to offer condolences and leave if mourners say they don't want to talk.But this family didn't feel that way. They were gracious and warm to us, and invited us to join other mourners who were with them.Experienced pilotThe captain of the ill-fated airliner, known only as Irianto -- many Indonesians go by one name -- had been with AirAsia for six years. He had worked for another airline in Indonesia for 13 years before that, and was an Indonesian Air Force pilot for a decade prior.READ: The latest on the searchWhen we arrived at his home, his wife, Widya Sukatri Putri, answered the door. She and Irianto have two children; a daughter named Angela who is about to turn 25, and a 7-year-old son named Arya. We told her we wanted to do a story about Irianto, that we hoped to find out what kind of husband and father he was; what kind of man and pilot he was. She invited us inside where we offered our condolences and asked if she would to talk to us on camera. She told us she wasn't sure if she wanted to talk, but invited us to come back later in the morning.We came back two hours later and the house was full of family and friends offering support to Widya, her children, and Irianto's elderly mother and father. What was taking place in the house was an Indonesian tradition known as a layat, a visitation by people when there is death in a family. There were dozens of people, old and young, sitting on the floor of Irianto's home. The house was so crowded that other mourners sat out in the front of the house, and some sat at tables that had been put in the middle of the closed off street.'Kind and loving' father and husbandWidya and Angela, her daughter, invited us to sit down with them, and it was there that they decided they did want to say a few words to us about Irianto. The portrait they painted about this man made it clear that he was kind and loving, fun and even-tempered, hard working and dedicated.READ: How can a modern airliner vanish?I marveled at how kind Irianto's wife and children were to us, how kind his parents were to us. They were suffering so much, yet they wanted to make us feel at home. I told his daughter not to worry about us. She told me her father had taught her to be hospitable.Angela is not ready to give up hope that someway, somehow he and other people on the plane might still be alive. But she knows that is unlikely and told us she is prepared to accept reality.This family made it very evident they were lucky to have Irianto in their lives. We said our goodbyes to this gracious family, realizing that the fated plane's pilot was also very lucky to have them.READ: Who was aboard AirAsia Flight QZ8501?</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101151334-nr-lkl-stevens-airasia-hamid-teacher-00012007-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101141003-pkg-hancocks-indonesia-bodies-arrive-00010802-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231122920-airasia-searcher-map-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101071713-01-airasia-0101-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231173852-airasia-grief-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231053007-airasia-search-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230132508-airasia-suitcase-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230194202-erin-dnt-stevens-airasia-bodies-and-debris-found-00004028-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071627-02-airasia-1229-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229111451-airasia-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231092416-airasia-search-pray-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182254-tsr-dnt-labott-airasia-crash-asian-airline-market-00000220-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229231219-ctn-intv-mh370-families-advice-to-airasia-familes-00000213-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228210218-nr-harlow-missing-airasia-update-00005323-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185851im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140721211119-mh17-black-box-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1374399">
        <title>Missed emails, hepatitis keep 15 from boarding doomed AirAsia Flight QZ8501</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/asia/airasia-missed-flight-fortunate-ones/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>It's an act of God that her father got hepatitis, says woman who canceled her family's flight</highlights>
        <highlights>Her brother forget to check emails, and it made their family miss the plane, another says</highlights>
        <highlights>Seven members of the two families who did not board QZ8501 are children</highlights>
        <highlights>Family members break down into tears when they hear the news of the missing plane</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T12:33:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Ben Brumfield, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Some may call it serendipity, others divine intervention. Either way, circumstances prevented two families from boarding doomed AirAsia Flight QZ8501.In one case, it was missed emails. In another, an illness in the family. As a result, 15 people -- seven of them children -- are alive and well.'Truly a miracle'It was no stroke of luck but an act of God that her father caught hepatitis, said Inge Goreti Ferdiningsih, because it made her family cancel their tickets on the AirAsia flight a day before it took off."We are extremely grateful, and God is really great," she said. "I believe that God is saving and protecting us, and this is truly a miracle."Inge Goreti booked the family vacation nine months earlier. Her father wasn't booked on the trip, and her younger sister was staying by his side.So, Inge Goreti could still have gone, with her husband and three children.'Feeling in my heart'The bags stood packed and ready, and the family was full of anticipation for the Singapore vacation. Christopher 10, Nadine, 7, and Felix, 5, were psyched about taking a local ship cruise, splashing at a water park and watching animals perform at Sea World.But then Inge Goreti's sister called from a hospital, where she had taken their father after he complained of stomach pains. The diagnosis: hepatitis.The news tugged at her. "I had this feeling in my heart that I wanted to be with my dad," Inge Goreti said.So, she called off the trip Saturday, a day before the flight.Christopher had a hard time accepting it. He was so looking forward to the trip and became very upset, she said.'We were late'An aversion to phone messages may have spared another family.Christianawati was going to ring in the New Year in Singapore with her family and her brother's family, she told a French news agency. Ten were traveling in all.But her brother forgot to check messages from AirAsia telling them that the flight was leaving two hours before the original departure time."They emailed and called us on December 15 and 16 to inform us, but we missed those calls," Christianawati, who goes by one name, told Agence France-Presse."So we arrived at the airport to check in for the 7:30 a.m. flight but were told our flights had been rescheduled to 5:30 a.m., and we were late. Of course we were angry," she said.Some family members pulled up in their car just in time to see the last passengers whisk past them into the boarding lounge, The Sydney Morning Herald reported.But Christianawati's family was traveling in two cars, and one was lagging behind. They just missed the flight.Then they heard the news."Maybe it is all God's plan that my family and I were not on the flight," Christianawati said. "It was a blessing in disguise."Une famille échappe par miracle au vol d'@AirAsia http://t.co/rn6srTP6IB @AirAsiaBlog #Indonésie #Christianawati pic.twitter.com/j3DpjhlUJJ'Broke down and cried'Early Sunday, at Inge Goreti's home, the phone rang -- a few times."We received calls from relatives regarding the plane that lost contact," Inge Goreti said. "We all broke down and cried."Sunday evening, the family went to church to give thanks.But mixed with Inge Goreti's tears of relief have been tears of sadness. She recognized names on Flight QZ8501's passenger manifest, she said.Friends and colleagues were on board.CNN's Dorrine Mendoza and translator Azieza Uhnavy contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013010-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-family-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013010-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-family-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013702-ferdiningsih-flight-booking-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013702-ferdiningsih-flight-booking-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101071713-01-airasia-0101-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231173852-airasia-grief-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231053007-airasia-search-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230132508-airasia-suitcase-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230194202-erin-dnt-stevens-airasia-bodies-and-debris-found-00004028-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071627-02-airasia-1229-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229111451-airasia-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231092416-airasia-search-pray-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182254-tsr-dnt-labott-airasia-crash-asian-airline-market-00000220-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229231219-ctn-intv-mh370-families-advice-to-airasia-familes-00000213-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228210218-nr-harlow-missing-airasia-update-00005323-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185852im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140721211119-mh17-black-box-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1375585">
        <title>Report: North Korean dictator would speak to South's President if 'mood' right</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/north-korea-kim-talks/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>Report: Kim Jong Un said, "We have no reason not to hold the highest-level talks"</highlights>
        <highlights>Last week, North Korea's government branded Park's election as fraudulent</highlights>
        <highlights>His words follow an offer by Seoul for minister level talks</highlights>
        <highlights>Sticking points between the two sides have led to breakdowns in diplomacy in the past</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T18:30:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Ben Brumfield, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Kim Jong Un is not officially on speaking terms with South Korean President Park Geun-hye. But on Thursday, in his New Year's address, he said that could change.Last week, North Korea's government news agency branded Park's election as fraudulent and her father -- himself a former President -- a dictator.But in his televised speech, for the first time ever, the communist leader said he'd talk with Park, South Korean news agency Yonhap reported."Depending on the mood and circumstances to be created, we have no reason not to hold the highest-level talks," Kim said.North Korea's state news agency did not publish those remarks in the official transcript of Kim's speech.His words may represent a small glacial budge, but that doesn't mean things will keep moving, Yonhap cautioned. Still, Kim spoke in detail about the need to improve North-South relations.Moments of thawIn between bellicose bantering -- particularly against the South's military partnership with the United States -- there have been momentary thaws. Three months ago, some of the North's highest officials paid a snap friendly visit to the South that sparked excited live television coverage.And this past Monday, Seoul's unification minister, Ryoo Kihl-jae, sent a fax to Pyongyang suggesting Cabinet ministers on both sides to meet in January, Yonhap reported."The South and the North will have to meet each other and discuss ways toward peaceful reunification," Ryoo later told journalists.Both want reunificationReunification is what both sides are pushing for."We should make fresh headway in the national reunification movement for this year," Kim said in Thursday's address, according to the official transcript published by the North's Korean Central News Agency.But they have pursued it on starkly different terms.President Park last year announced a 2015 road map to reunification, which she laid out in a speech in April in Dresden, Germany, Yonhap has reported.Dresden was part of East Germany, back when Germany was divided between the democratic West and Soviet Communist East, and South Koreans have drawn hope from that country's reunification for the possible realization of their own. Park's talk has been called the Dresden Declaration.Free market supportSince then, the South has sought support from its international allies for Park's reunification plan, selling a single Korea as an economic boon to a global free market, Yonhap has reported.The North has railed against this, fearing the economically muscular South, aided by other capitalist countries, would, in a reunification, effectively digest the North. Kim does not want Seoul's allies involved and criticized the South's diplomatic efforts again on Thursday."To go on a tour around foreign countries touting for 'international cooperation' in resolving the inter-Korean relations issue, the one related with our nation, is a humiliating treachery of leaving its destiny in the hands of outside forces," he said.But Kim's conciliatory words following after the South's offer to talk again, and his hints of moving talks up to the highest level could be significant.Ryoo, who extended that invitation, is also Park's right hand in her reunification effort, Yonhap reported. He said his offer to talk was in line with the 2015 road map.Fragile situationBut Kim's speech was not all conciliatory. Some of it was bellicose.He commended his forces' "showdown with the imperialists," possibly a reference to caustic reactions to South Korean-U.S. military exercises.The dictator also praised political killings in his own ranks."Our Party detected and purged the anti-Party, counterrevolutionary factionalists at an opportune time and with a correct decision," the KCNA speech transcript said.South Korean intelligence officials said that members of the North's ruling party were shot by firing squad for viewing a South Korean soap opera.And there are additional pressure points that have derailed Seoul-Pyongyang agreements in the past, such as the floating of messages via balloon by activists in the South into the North. North Korean soldiers opening fire on these balloons last year struck South Korean territory. There were no reported injuries or damage.The North sees the balloons as a violation of its borders. The South sees them as an exercise of free speech.The South imposed an economic sanctions package on the North in 2010 over the attack on a South Korean navy ship that killed 46 sailors. Seoul demands that Pyongyang take responsibility for torpedoing the vessel before it lifts the sanctions.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230184453-lead-dnt-brown-north-korea-behind-sony-hack-00012318-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218105623-south-korea-christmas-tree-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218103108-n-korea-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218110151-4minute-pop-group-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218111314-north-korea-statues-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218104042-n-korea-4-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218104424-n-korea-5-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218105623-south-korea-christmas-tree-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218103108-n-korea-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218110151-4minute-pop-group-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218111314-north-korea-statues-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218104042-n-korea-4-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218104424-n-korea-5-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218105623-south-korea-christmas-tree-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141219161315-sony-interview-poster-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224135131-exp-martin-libicki-north-korea-offline-00000908-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217070125-the-interview-franco-rogen-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155523-inside-north-korea-computer-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130329113834-01-kim-jong-un-0329-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218025504-sony-interview-hack-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141110205151-kim-jong-un-military-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218110151-4minute-pop-group-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141205095815-merrill-newman-50s-kuwol-comrades-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119004344-dnt-mckenzie-north-korean-refugee-00012419-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141103134739-north-korea-defector-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141117213214-michael-kirby-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141117180858-pkg-hancocks-north-korea-human-rights-abuses-00001008-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141011014136-pkg-mckenzie-china-needs-kim-00014011-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185853im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140101063453-lklv-penhaul-kim-jung-un-new-year-00002808-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1376521">
        <title>Teen bailed after being placed in care for drawing on Hong Kong protest site wall</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/02/world/asia/hong-kong-chalk-girl-protests/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>Girl, 14, bailed after being arrested and put into children's home for drawing on wall at former protest site</highlights>
        <highlights>Court considering application from police that she be removed from father's care</highlights>
        <highlights>Girl says she has no regrets about taking part in pro-democracy protest</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T09:23:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Vicky Wong, for CNN</author>
        <content>Hong Kong (CNN) -- A 14-year-old girl has been bailed after being arrested and threatened with removal from her father's care for drawing flowers on a wall at a pro-democracy protest site in Hong Kong.The girl was caught in the early hours of December 23 at a staircase leading to the Central Government Offices in the city's Admiralty district and was detained by police for 17 hours, said Patricia Ho, the lawyer acting for the teen.A judge ruled in a youth court on Monday that the girl should be sent to a children's home for 20 days until January 19. However, on Wednesday evening the girl was released on bail after her lawyers filed an application for a re-hearing on bail conditions for the girl on Tuesday.The city's High Court allowed the girl to return home to live with her father up to January 19 provided she continues her studies and obeys a curfew from 10 p.m. until 6 a.m. unless accompanied by her father, sister or a social worker.A spokesman for the city's social welfare department told CNN the department would write a report on the girl's case, which would look into the assessment of the needs of the care or protection of children or juveniles.They said the department could not specifically comment on the case as it has entered the judicial process but said the report should be published some time before the girl's court date on January 19.Now: teen drew flowers with chalk on the wall. Lots of police officers are detaining her &amp; others. #UmbrellaMovement pic.twitter.com/zwNM6S8crfThe wall, known as the "Lennon Wall," was once covered with colorful Post-it notes and messages of support for the recent pro-democracy protests in Hong Kong. When the protests were cleared, the notes were removed as well.Protesters started placing notes on the wall as a show of defiance after police used tear gas on demonstrators at the start of the protest, which led to a two-month occupation of the main road outside the Central Government Office.The wall was named after the late Beatles star John Lennon and contained messages of support for the protests and references to his song "Imagine."'Don't give up'In an interview with a local newspaper Ming Pao Daily, the teen said she did not regret taking part in the pro-democracy protests.The girl thanked protesters for supporting her and urged people to continue supporting the protests."Don't give up on this movement, we've been doing this for three months, there needs to be more people, not just me alone."News of the arrest angered activists and prompted some small demonstrations in the city on New Year's Eve. Twenty-seven protesters staged a "die-in" at the International Finance Center (IFC), the site of one of the city's biggest shopping malls, and around 40 protesters attempted to write messages of support on "Lennon Wall" in the early hours of New Year's Day.On New Year's Eve some protesters started drawing on the road as a protest outside the children's home in the city's Tuen Mun district, where the teenager was held.Ho said the police application for the girl to be removed from her father's care was "premature and disproportionate."She added that the girl's father is seriously hearing impaired and cannot understand the case."It wasn't an application by the Social Welfare Department as it usually would be," she said. "Police threw in a bunch of facts they obtained about the family in a very superficial manner."Gary Tsang, who participated in Hong Kong's pro-democracy street occupations, told CNN the teen was "an innocent political prisoner" and the use of the law in this case was "obviously politically motivated.""The government fears young people as they thinks young people have nothing to lose," he said."Chalk-girl"drew this,detained 17hrs in police station&amp;sent to Children's Home to wait for her next trial til mid-Jan pic.twitter.com/xrcbrPp2EgThe move comes after police also made an application for a care or protection order for a teenage boy who was arrested during the clearance of another protest site in Mong Kok last month. The court file said the boy's parents failed to exercise proper guardianship over him.The court dates for both teenagers will take place in January.Continued resistanceA small protest camp outside the Legislative Council still remains and there is a small police presence on the site. Police officers are guarding Lennon Wall and remove all notes posted to it at the end of each day.New Year's Eve countdown events at popular shopping districts such as Causeway Bay and Tsim Sha Tsui were canceled because of fears that protesters would attempt to hijack the events.Since the protest sites were cleared, demonstrators have resorted to other forms of protest such as the so-called "shopping revolution," which involves protestors blocking the sidewalks and flooding shopping districts every night with yellow umbrellas.Hong Kong Police have not responded to requests for comment.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007143137-hong-kong-goddess-umbrella-split-horizontal-gallery.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007130820-hong-kong-umbrella-canopy-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140928163233-hong-kong-protests-sept-28-05-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007121713-yellow-umbrella-ribbons-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007130347-hong-kong-umbrella-protest-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007131240-hong-kong-wall-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007125327-hong-kong-protest-post-it-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007125854-hong-kong-banner-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007143137-hong-kong-goddess-umbrella-split-topics.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007130820-hong-kong-umbrella-canopy-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140928163233-hong-kong-protests-sept-28-05-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007121713-yellow-umbrella-ribbons-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007130347-hong-kong-umbrella-protest-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007131240-hong-kong-wall-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007125327-hong-kong-protest-post-it-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007125854-hong-kong-banner-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007143137-hong-kong-goddess-umbrella-split-horizontal-gallery.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007083024-pkg-watson-hk-protest-art-00002108-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210145801-hong-kong-protest-joshua-wong-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210180009-hong-kong-protest-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210151535-hong-kong-protest-tents-clearance-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141204104157-occupy-central-leaders-police-station-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141201192559-hong-kong-police-batons-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141202115845-joshua-wong-tent-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141128135742-joshua-wong-court-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140922085548-hong-kong-youth-joshua-wong-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002173551-hong-kong-leung-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007133500-cy-leung-joshua-wong-split-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016162308-cy-leung-press-conference-thursday-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141201192559-hong-kong-police-batons-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015110316-hong-kong-ken-tsang-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008153840-hong-kong-umbrella-man-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141004115644-04-hk-1004-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007103528-china-news-stand-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007123158-4-hk-police-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005000425-natpkg-hong-kong-protests-10-04-14-00005718-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141003154806-hong-kong-clashes-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002161554-china-soldier-hk-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141001200450-hong-kong-tear-gas-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185923im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140929104244-hong-kong-monday-2-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1377606">
        <title>3 soldiers killed in Kashmir gunfight between India and Pakistan</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/kashmir-violence/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>Pakistani military says Indian side shot first</highlights>
        <highlights>Indian military: Pakistani rangers shot and killed an Indian soldier on New Year's Eve</highlights>
        <highlights>Bilateral ceasefire agreement held for years, but there have been recent breaches</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T21:22:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Mukhtar Ahmad and Adeel Raja, CNN</author>
        <content>Kashmir (CNN) -- The sound of gunfire marked New Year's Eve in the tense disputed region of Kashmir between India and Pakistan.Pakistani rangers shot and killed an Indian soldier, India's military said. India's military shot and killed two Pakistani rangers, Pakistan's military said.Both sides claimed that the other started the gunfight.Indian military spokesman Dharminder Parikh said Pakistani rangers opened fire unprovoked at Indian positions in the Samba sector of Indian-administered Kashmir as the old year was coming to a close. A second Indian border soldier was wounded in the fight, he said.Pakistan's Punjab Rangers said that their Indian counterparts had a meeting, and when two rangers contacted them, the Indian side opened fire. The two were wounded and later died, they said.The two nuclear-armed South Asian neighbors had agreed to a bilateral ceasefire in border regions in November 2003, and the agreement held for years.But there have been breaches in recent years.Kashmir has been in the throes of separatist violence since 1989, which has claimed over 43,000 lives.Indian soldiers killed in gunfight with militants in Kashmir</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1378581">
        <title>With climate change, Himalayas' future is warmer, not necessarily brighter</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/asia/nepal-climate-change-himalayas/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>Recent deadly mountain incidents in Himalayas have created concern about climate change</highlights>
        <highlights>Avalanches are more frequent and of greater magnitude, says Sherpa</highlights>
        <highlights>Landslides and floods have made farming more difficult in recent years</highlights>
        <highlights>"Sorting out what's due to climate change and what's not is difficult," says Himalaya expert</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T03:49:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Madison Park, CNN</author>
        <content>Dolakha, Nepal (CNN) -- As snow layered the trail before him, Hari Chaudhary thought it was odd. The veteran trekking guide had never seen snow on the trail in early October.The popular 21-day Annapurna Circuit takes trekkers in a horseshoe-shaped route around a majestic segment of the Himalayas in Nepal.On the 10th day of the tour, Chaudhary and his clients, two young Israeli women, were descending from the highest point of the trail, Thorung La Pass, to the next destination, a walk that would normally take about seven hours.Now, after more than 10 hours of heading downhill, the snow pelted.The flurry fell heavier and faster, obstructing their vision. There was nowhere to stop or rest; they had to keep walking."You couldn't see the trail, there was snow everywhere, making it easy to get lost," said Chaudhary. "It was all white, in the distance you could only see shadows of people walking."Some wandered off the trail.As the blizzard continued, their feet sunk into the snow pile. As their steps became heavier, they began to cry.As the hours passed, Chaudhary could make out backpacks and supplies strewn on the snow."There were people who had fallen, or were stuck or resting along the way. I couldn't tell if I saw a dead body."Conditions in the Himalayas can be cruel. But trekkers dying in snowstorms on the Annapurna Circuit is almost unheard of -- until this year.Deadly yearNepal, known for its fabled Himalayas including Mount Everest, has endured a deadly, tragic year.In April, a hanging glacial mass collapsed and tumbled through a dangerous route on Everest, killing 16 Sherpas in the worst single disaster.Months later, an unseasonal snowstorm struck Annapurna, killing at least 43 people including locals and foreign tourists.Were the disasters just prone to happen or was climate change a factor?Everest mountaineers have spoken of changes they've witnessed for years."In my first journey, there was snow and ice," said Apa Sherpa, a retired mountaineer who made his first summit in 1990. "Now we can see more rock. It's more dangerous ... the glacier's melting, the ice is falling, there's rocks falling more."After a record 21 summits of Everest, he has no doubt that conditions are changing rapidly.Dawa Stephen Sherpa, who has been climbing Everest since 2006, agreed: "Our observations show that seracs are peeling off the mountains much quicker and we're seeing avalanches much more frequently and of greater magnitude."Whether the deadly disasters in Nepal this year can be linked to climate change is debatable."I am leery of attributing everything bad in nature to climate change," said Jeffrey Kargel, senior associate research scientist at the University of Arizona who studies the Himalayas."Sorting out what's specifically due to climate change and what's not is a difficult and sometimes impossible task. That said, it's clear climate is changing all over the world, including in Nepal."While it's difficult to blame any single incident on climate change, there's evidence of an increasingly warming Himalayas.Temperatures in the central Himalayas increased by about 0.6 degrees Celsius per decade between 1977 and 2000, according to one study. In the Tibetan Plateau, the average temperature in Lhasa rose by 1.35 degrees Celsius in 30 years, according to a report by International Centre for Integrated Mountain Development.The impact of climate change includes accelerated glacial melt, irregular rainfall, changes in the monsoon season and greater risk of catastrophes such as avalanches, landslides and floods.Natural disasters always happen, regardless of climate change, experts say. What's worrisome is that disasters in the Himalayas are becoming more common.Extreme flooding hit Pakistan in 2012 and landslides and flooding washed away streets and killed hundreds in 2013 at a Himalayan holy site in Kedernath, India. Unusually early and heavy monsoon rains triggered that disaster, in which two months of rain poured in two days."These extreme rare events, they're not rare anymore," Kargel said.Water towers of AsiaThe Himalayas stretch from the eastern corner of Afghanistan, through Nepal to the northern tip of Myanmar. They contain snow packs and glaciers with freshwater that feed 10 major Asian rivers, including the Ganges, Brahmaputra, Mekong, Yellow and Yangtze, giving life to the continent's farms.Disruptions to the Himalayas could affect agriculture, as well as water and food security for Asian countries including the two most populous countries in the world -- India and China.Nepal sits sandwiched between these two countries, which are among the world's biggest contributors to greenhouse gas emissions.But Nepal emits 0.025% of the world's greenhouse gas emissions, according to estimates."We have not swallowed poison, yet we are being poisoned," said Dr. Govind Raj Pokharel, vice chairman of the Nepal's planning commission. "We haven't done anything against nature or contributed to climate change, but we are majorly affected."Farmers at riskIn Nepal, climate change is already impacting lives and livelihood, scientists say."Climate change is making things worse," said Deepak K.C., senior program officer for integrated climate risk management at the United Nations Development Program. "There are lots of dry spurts, interspersed with heavy rain in a short period of time that's causing flooding."Farmers say that pests they've never seen before are eating their crops. The monsoon rains they've traditionally expected to arrive in June have become inconsistent, many say."We depend on timely rainfall for crop cultivation," said Purnimaya Thamang, a farmer who lives in a small village near the foot of the Himalayas. "We may not be able to feed ourselves or have the proper yield. The rain is either too late, too little or too much."It wasn't like this before, they say.Nepal's mountains are encircled with terrace farms where families have tilled the soil for generations. More than 70% of Nepalis work in agriculture and most are subsistence farmers.Many farmers, like Ganesh Thami, have seen landslides and floods destroy their livelihoods. He woke up several years ago to his house trembling as a flood swept over his farmland."The river beating the stones made drumming sounds that kept growing. I heard the sound of the boulders rolling with the water. It felt like an earthquake," said Thami, who lost his farm in Dolakha, near the Himalayas.Dolakha is identified as one of the most vulnerable districts to landslides according to a national study on climate change conducted by the Nepalese government.The farmers say their livelihood is becoming harder and they don't know why."The people that are hit the hardest are not the ones causing the climate change," said David Molden, director general of the Kathmandu-based International Centre for Integrated Mountain Development. "That's the important message. The poorest people in the world are emitting the least amount of carbon, (yet) they're the ones who have to adapt dramatically to these changes."In harms wayOne of the issues is that some villages and homes are cropping up too close to a river or in dangerous areas prone to landslides or floods."People who are building are unaware that they're in dire jeopardy," Kargel said. "Right now, there's uncontrolled growth, in very vulnerable places, with houses sitting on river bluffs."The mountains have always carried risk of landslides, avalanches and snowstorms even without climate change. But new developments in vulnerable areas exacerbate the risks of making them casualty events."The Himalayas are changing, the way people are living in the Himalayas is changing too," said Molden. "People are living closer to the river, there are more trekkers and mountain climbers."As Everest has become more commercial, the number of expeditions has increased. In 2013, 658 climbers summited the peak, compared with 192 two decades ago. About 20,000 people a year now trek around the Annapurnas.More people climbing and trekking means a greater probability of disasters that impact tourists and local hires."People were not prepared"It's riskier for local hires, like Hari Chaudhary, who are exposed to greater risks because of repeated trips."Why would you want to go to the mountains? I only do it because I need to survive and I need the money," he said.The only opportunities for uneducated, landless men are to take a construction job in the Middle East or work in tourism, said Chaudhary, a lanky man with a wiry frame. He has to support his wife and two kids.During the blizzard, he guided his two clients to safety after 12 hours. While dozens died, went missing or had their hands blackened from frostbite, he and his two Israeli hikers survived without injuries.For a day's work of carrying 50 pounds of gear and guiding tourists, he earns $10.The Annapurna snowstorm was the effect of Cyclone Hudhud, which lashed India and wound up north in Nepal in October. Hundreds of tourists and local hires were stranded when the storms hit."People were not prepared, they didn't get the warning signals, like they should have," said Molden.While the Annapurna event cannot be definitively ruled as a climate change-related disaster, it can't be ruled out either, scientists say."The speculation to the link to climate change is we're getting more intense rainfall or precipitation," said Molden. "It's so hard to say that event was due to climate change. All of these things have a relation. To prove that would be difficult."Chaudhary attributes his survival to the rings of ice that formed around his ankles, which blocked snow from seeping into his bright orange Nikes, saving his feet from frostbite.Just three days later, Chaudhary laced the same sneakers and headed back to the mountains to guide another group, glancing upward to the clouds that, for him and others, were becoming increasingly difficult to decipher.This story was made possible by a reporting grant from the International Center for Journalists. A second part about solutions will run in 2015. Journalist Manesh Shrestha also contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015105554-01-annapurna-file-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172609-annapurna-bodies-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172956-nepal-guide-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140419162007-01-everest-avalance-0419-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140419182919-12-everest---khumbu-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172649-apa-sherpa-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130619232713-india-monsoon-13-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230173137-nepal-terrace-farms-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182416-nepal-farmers-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015105554-01-annapurna-file-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172609-annapurna-bodies-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172956-nepal-guide-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140419162007-01-everest-avalance-0419-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140419182919-12-everest---khumbu-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172649-apa-sherpa-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130619232713-india-monsoon-13-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230173137-nepal-terrace-farms-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182416-nepal-farmers-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017130635-map-annapurna-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017130635-map-annapurna-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141019192954-cnni-dnt-udas-himalaya-nepal-hikers-00020025-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015154331-nepal-trekkers-killed-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015213519-deadly-disasters-in-the-himalayas-ts-orig-00002412-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172649-apa-sherpa-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140430101150-mount-everest-avalanche-ogwyn-newday-00042901-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140424055800-exp-mount-everest-avalanche-expeditions-deaths-00002001-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140418114506-nepal-everest-avalanche-deadliest-accident-00020514-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140418114508-nepal-everest-avalanche-deadliest-accident-00000830-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230185341-himalayas-terrain-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230173036-nepal-planning-official-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172815-nepal-farmers-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230173137-nepal-terrace-farms-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230172956-nepal-guide-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230192200-nepal-guide-shoes-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185951im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1379645">
        <title>Ex-Korean Air executive in nuts scandal detained by prosecutors</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180731/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/asia/korean-air-nuts-scandal/index.html?hpt=ias_c2</url>
        <highlights>Prosecutors get an arrest warrant Tuesday night</highlights>
        <highlights>Heather Cho ordered a Korean Air plane back to the gate in early December</highlights>
        <highlights>She reacted after a flight attendant served nuts in a bag instead of on a plate</highlights>
        <highlights>She later apologized and resigned from her role as vice president</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T01:24:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By K.J. Kwon and Steve Almasy, CNN</author>
        <content>Seoul, South Korea (CNN) -- A former Korean Air executive who sparked outrage earlier this month by kicking a flight attendant off a plane for serving macadamia nuts the wrong way is being detained by police in Seoul.Heather Cho, the 40-year-old daughter of Korean Air's chairman, is in the South Seoul Detention Facility, the Seoul Western District Prosecutor's Office said. Officials gave no other details, other than the investigation into the incident is ongoing.A spokesman for the office, Lee Kwang-woo, said an arrest warrant was approved because "the necessity was recognized because of the graveness of the case and there was an attempt to systematically cover up the charges since the beginning of the incident."Cho resigned from her post as a vice president at the company in the aftermath of the incident earlier this month on a flight from New York's JFK airport to South Korea's Incheon International Airport.She ordered that the plane turn back to the gate and that a flight attendant be removed because she was served nuts in a bag instead of on a plate in first class.Although her role put her in charge of in-flight service, Cho was a passenger and was not flying in an official capacity.Amid public anger over her behavior, she and her father both apologized for the incident. Cho, whose Korean name is Cho Hyun-ah, said she accepted "full responsibility" for what happened.Last week, prosecutors said an arrest warrant might cover charges of violating aviation safety rules, including a change in a flight plan, assault on a plane, coercion and interference in the execution of duty. The warrant was approved Tuesday night.When contacted by CNN, the press office for Korean Air said it had no comment on the latest development.'Violent language'Testimony from crew members and passengers confirmed that Cho used "violent language in a loud voice," which may not be compliant with an aviation safety law that requires cooperation of passengers on a flight, the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport said earlier this month.The captain of the plane has also faced criticism for obeying Cho's demands to turn back the plane and remove the flight attendant.The airline faces possible disciplinary action from the government because of the captain's failure to command and supervise crew members to ensure the safe operation of the flight, the ministry said last week.CNN's Jethro Mullen and Elizabeth Joseph contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102185952im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
</ns2:topic>
