<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns2:topic xmlns:ns2="http://schema/" topicid="1381421">
    <topicname>Europe</topicname>
    <news newsid="1382645">
        <title>Italian coast guard rescues ship carrying migrants</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/europe/italy-migrants-ship/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Rescuers are trying to restart the boat's engines, the coast guard says</highlights>
        <highlights>The ship without any crew is carrying 450 migrants</highlights>
        <highlights>This is the second time this week the Italian coast guard has rescued such a vessel</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T02:04:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Sara Delgrossi and Dana Ford, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Italian authorities responded late Thursday to a ship without any crew that was carrying 450 migrants, that country's coast guard said.It's the second time this week Italy's coast guard has rescued such a vessel."Because of the difficult weather conditions, the ship can only be reached by air. From what we know, the ship, which flies the flag of Sierra Leone, would have hundreds of migrants on board," the Italian air force said in a statement.It said the cargo ship Ezadeen was in at a standstill because of a blackout.The migrants launched an SOS, said Floriana Segreto, a spokeswoman for the Italian coast guard. Women and children are thought to be on the ship.By early Friday morning, the vessel remained at a standstill 58 miles (93 kilometers) off the coast of the city of Crotone in the Ionian Sea, the coast guard said, where rescuers were trying to restart the boat's engines.On Wednesday, a freighter carrying 768 people, most believed to be migrants from war-torn Syria, docked safely in the southern port of Gallipoli after the coast guard seized control.The Italian coast guard told CNN a "real disaster" was avoided when authorities boarded the Blue Sky M after the crew apparently jumped ship.Italian coast guard commander Filippo Marini said the vessel was cruising on autopilot toward the rocky Italian coast at 6 nautical miles per hour. The course of the vessel was reversed to avoid a collision with the rocks.The coast guard said a collision would not only have led to the deaths of passengers but would also have created an environmental disaster.CNN's Livia Borghese contributed to this report.</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1383631">
        <title>UK Ebola patient asks for experimental treatment</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/europe/uk-ebola/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>A health care worker diagnosed with the virus is asking for experimental drug therapy</highlights>
        <highlights>She is the first to be diagnosed with Ebola in the UK</highlights>
        <highlights>She fell ill after returning from West Africa as a medical volunteer</highlights>
        <highlights>A woman in the Scottish Highlands has tested negative for Ebola, government says</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T17:53:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Laura Smith-Spark, Nic Robertson, Alexander Felton and Deborah E. Bloom, CNN</author>
        <content>London (CNN) -- A Scottish woman diagnosed with Ebola is now asking for experimental treatment of the virus.Pauline Cafferkey, 39, of Glasgow, is sitting up in her hospital bed, reading and talking, according to a statement from the Royal Free Hospital in London. "However, the next few days will be crucial," said Dr. Michael Jacobs, an infectious diseases consultant. "The disease has a variable course and we will know much more in a week's time."Cafferkey is the first person to be diagnosed with the virus on UK soil. British media outlets have said she is a public health nurse who was part of a 30-strong team of medical volunteers deployed to Sierra Leone in West Africa by the UK government last month in a joint endeavor with Save the Children.She traveled via Casablanca, Morocco, and London Heathrow Airport before arriving at Glasgow Airport on a British Airways flight late Sunday, the health agency NHS Scotland said. After feeling unwell, she sought medical attention and was reportedly transferred to London on a military aircraft fitted with an isolation pod.The Royal Free Hospital is equipped with a high-level isolation unit, with access restricted to specially trained medical staff. A specially designed tent, with controlled ventilation, is set up over the patient's bed.A British volunteer nurse, William Pooley, was successfully treated in the unit following his return home from Sierra Leone in August after being diagnosed with Ebola.'Extremely low' riskUK authorities are working to trace those who have come into contact with Cafferkey.The Scottish government has set up a special number for people to call if they traveled on the same London Heathrow-to-Glasgow flight as Cafferkey.British Airways said it was working closely with health authorities in England and Scotland and would help with any information needed."The safety and security of our customers and crew is always our top priority and the risk to people on board that individual flight is extremely low," the airline said.Ebola patients become infectious only after they display symptoms, such as fever and vomiting. The deadly virus is spread through contact with bodily fluids.A Downing Street spokesman told CNN that British Prime Minister David Cameron and Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon had discussed the procedures in place to handle such a case."They agreed that both governments would remain in close touch and ensure everything possible was done to support the patient and, although the risk to the general population remained low, all measures would be taken to protect public health."Scottish woman tests negativeMeanwhile, a woman in the Northwest Highlands of Scotland who'd fallen ill tested negative for Ebola, the Scottish government said Tuesday.A spokesman for the government said the woman had been in West Africa recently, though she had no direct contact with anyone with Ebola."A patient at Aberdeen Royal Infirmary has tested negative for Ebola," a Tuesday news release said. "The individual was transferred to the hospital by the Scottish Ambulance Service yesterday after falling ill while visiting Torridon in the Scottish Highlands."According to UK government guidelines, humanitarian workers returning from Ebola-affected countries in West Africa who've been at high risk of exposure are expected to monitor their own health for 21 days after they get home.As of December 24, at least 7,693 people had died in the current Ebola outbreak, centered in Liberia, Sierra Leone and Guinea, the World Health Organization said. There have been at least 19,695 cases.CNN's Bharati Naik contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140801152641-pkg-soares-uk-london-ebola-preps-00000905-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175823-tsr-dnt-johns-cdc-scare-00000612-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210100917-nr-time-person-of-the-year-2014-ebola-00000829-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010140326-01-ebola-liberia-1010-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141104111536-ebola-restrictions-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141028065645-emile-ouamouno-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141009182112-this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-still-from-graphic-package-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141024150658-holmes-race-for-ebola-vaccine-00003921-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012125025-ebola-virus-structure-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006091841-03-ebola-1006-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017013751-pkg-simon-risk-of-ebola-on-plane-00001919-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141019151035-spain-ebola-tests-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015170302-01-ebola-1015-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020004450-pkg-elbagir-ebola-orphans-00021929-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013174627-cdc-ebola-guidelines-lead-gfx-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008115210-excalibur-ebola-dog-victim-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014015016-pkg-tomkins-ebola-protective-gear-00005610-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141001224002-texas-health-presbyterian-hospital-dallas-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140728125203-04-ebola-guinea-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190523im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140327172929-who-officials-ebola-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1384659">
        <title>Kremlin critic Alexey Navalny arrested hours after sentencing</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/europe/russia-alexei-navalny-case/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Navalny tweeted a selfie on the way to join protesters who support him</highlights>
        <highlights>Kremlin critic Alexey Navalny and his brother Oleg have been convicted of fraud</highlights>
        <highlights>Alexey Navalny's 3.5 year sentence was suspended, he was also fined</highlights>
        <highlights>His brother Oleg received a 3.5-year prison term and fine</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T03:48:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Laura Smith-Spark, Matthew Chance and Alla Eshchenko, CNN</author>
        <content>Moscow (CNN) -- Just hours after he was found guilty of fraud in a politically charged trial and given a suspended sentence, blogger and Kremlin critic Alexey Navalny was detained after he broke house arrest and went to join a protest against the court's verdict.He didn't try to hide what he was doing: He tweeted a picture of himself on the Moscow metro as he headed to the demonstration. "Under house arrest, yes, but today I very much want to be with you. That is why I am also going," said the caption on the photo.News agency Interfax reported that Navalny was detained by police and was returned to his home, instead of being taken to jail. He was on house arrest for a conviction in a 2009 case.Домашний арест-это да, но сегодня мне очень хочется быть с вами. Поэтому я тоже еду. #Манежка pic.twitter.com/xkWGX0Hp4FEarlier, Navalny was in court, where he got a three-and-a-half year suspended sentence for the fraud conviction, while his brother, Oleg, also convicted of fraud, was given a prison term of the same length.Both were hit with steep fines, but only Oleg Navalny was ordered to pay.When the sentence was read, Alexey Navalny shouted out in anger and frustration with the judgment against his brother.The brothers denied charges of embezzling 30 million rubles ($540,000) from a Russian subsidiary of French cosmetics company Yves Rocher between 2008 and 2012.There were strong feelings among some in Moscow that the brothers should not have been sentenced as they were. Despite the biting winter cold, their supporters gathered near the Kremlin in Moscow's Manezhnaya square Tuesday night to rally against the verdicts.A Facebook page promoting the event predicted that thousands would attend, but the numbers were far smaller as the protest got underway.The sentencing hearing was originally scheduled for January 15 -- when a big rally was planned -- but was brought forward at a day's notice, leading Navalny's supporters to slam what they said was an attempt to suppress protest.Many people have left Moscow ahead of the New Year public holiday, making it harder to muster a crowd.The protest is likely considered illegal because Navalny's supporters didn't have enough time to apply for the permissions required under Russian law, raising the prospect of a confrontation between protesters and police.After the sentencing, Navalny supporters also accused the Kremlin of using Oleg Navalny as leverage against his brother.However, they did voice surprise that the sentences were not tougher. Prosecutors had asked for Alexey Navalny to be given a 10-year prison sentence and Oleg to receive an eight-year term.A corruption-fighting lawyer, Alexey Navalny famously branded the ruling United Russia party -- founded by President Vladimir Putin -- "the party of crooks and thieves."He was a prominent organizer of mass street protests three years ago and has attacked corruption in Russian government, using his blog and social media.Before Tuesday's ruling he was under house arrest after he was convicted last year of misappropriating $500,000 worth of state-owned timber, in what he told CNN was a fabricated case.CNN's Alla Eshchenko and Matthew Chance reported from Moscow, Laura Smith-Spark wrote in London and Gena Somra reported in Atlanta. CNN's Erin McLaughlin also contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190540im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230022006-lok-mclaughlin-russia-kremlin-critic-navalny-guilty-sentence-00001926-story-body.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1386637">
        <title>What's behind conviction of Russian opposition activist Alexei Navalny?</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2013/07/20/world/europe/russia-alexei-navalny-explainer/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny has been convicted of misappropriation</highlights>
        <highlights>A court freed him from detention on July 19, pending an appeal of the court's ruling against him</highlights>
        <highlights>Navalny famously branded the ruling United Russia party "the party of crooks and thieves"</highlights>
        <highlights>He claims his trial was politically motivated, an allegation the authorities have denied</highlights>
        <date>2013-07-20T14:29:00.000+01:00</date>
        <author>By Susannah Cullinane, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Kremlin critic and Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny has been convicted of misappropriating $500,000 worth of state-owned timber.A court freed him from detention on July 19, pending an appeal of the court's ruling against him.Navalny has been campaigning for the Moscow mayoralty -- officially registering as a candidate the day before his conviction -- and there have been allegations his trial has been politically-motivated.Russian authorities insist that is not the case.LATEST: "I'll win Moscow," says NavalnyWho is Alexei Navalny?Navalny is a corruption fighting lawyer who famously branded the ruling United Russia party -- founded by President Vladimir Putin -- "the party of crooks and thieves."He has been a prominent organizer of street protests and has attacked corruption in Russian government, using his blog and social media.In a 2011 article entitled "Russia rising: The Blogger Who Is Putin's Greatest Challenger," TIME magazine's Simon Shuster said before 2010 Navalny had been known "only to a fairly small online community."But in November 2010, Shuster said, Navalny "blew the whistle" on what he said was a $4 billion embezzlement scheme at the state-run oil pipeline operator Transneft -- a claim vigorously denied by the head of the company and Russian president Vladimir Putin.In January 2011, Transneft's boss branded the claims inaccurate, according to Reuters news agency. And in September that year, state-run news agency RIA Novosti quoted President Putin as saying no crimes had been committed by Transneft."The leaked documents he presented as evidence, which he posted on his blog, caused a sensation in the Russian and international press, and Navalny soon became known as Russia's top crusader against corruption," wrote TIME's Shuster.OPINION: Putin a hypocrite on Snowden, NavalnyIn 2012, TIME included Navalny on its list of "The World's 100 Most Influential people."Russian chess legend and opposition activist Garry Kasparov wrote the entry on Navalny -- then 35 -- saying he was -- "at the vanguard" of data dissidents.How much of a threat does he pose to Putin/Kremlin?CNN's Moscow correspondent Phil Black said Navalny's passion, charisma, fierce language and commitment to fighting corruption inspired many to join him in protesting on the streets.Maria Lipman, a political analyst at the Carnegie Moscow Center think-tank, said during the 2011 and 2012 protests over alleged fraud in Russia's parliamentary and presidential elections Navalny was "by far the most popular figure.""Navalny quite bravely took on some of the very influential people in Russia," she said.Lipman said Navalny was a fearless and very talented public politician who had managed to "beat the system that Putin built" to keep outsiders out of the political framework.Navalny presented "a serious political challenge as a result of his unique personality and his amazing energy," she said. "He was able, as a result, to build a following.""He's become a popular figure but he cannot be described as the leader of the opposition," she said. "He is the most prominent civic figure."What are the details of his case?A court in the city of Kirov on July 18 found Navalny guilty of misappropriating about $500,000 in a lumber deal when he was an adviser to the Kirov region's governor. It sentenced him to five years in prison.Was the verdict expected?The day before his trial began in April this year, Navalny told CNN's Phil Black he knew he would be convicted and that it was likely he would be jailed."I've been investigating corruption in state-run companies by government officials for the last six years. These people steal billions. I'm making it harder for them to steal and they understand my anti-corruption work is a threat."Asked if he believed he had any chance of winning the case he replied: "Of course not. They didn't fabricate this case to allow that and it's obvious for me it's going to be a guilty verdict."Why would he be jailed unless he was guilty?The court found Navalny guilty but his lawyers are appealing the verdict. Russian law forbids convicted criminals running for political office.Talking to Phil Black before the trial began, Navalny said: "It's true one of Putin's goals in this trial is to stop me from being involved in politics but this law only exists in Putin's system and our goal is to destroy Putin's system."Lipman said she also believed the verdict was politically motivated. "The government is using law enforcement and judiciary machines to lock up a man who is a political challenge. There is hardly any doubt that the verdict in the courtroom was not made by the judge himself," she said."There is every reason to suggest that the verdict announced on July 18 in Kirov was a decision made somewhere very high in the Kremlin executive."Russian authorities have always insisted Navalny's prosecution is not political.But a senior investigator recently admitted his colleagues had fast tracked their work in Navalny's case because of his criticism of Russia's political system."The suspect is doing his best to draw attention to himself; one could even say he is teasing the authorities," said Vladimir Markin, the spokesman of Russia's Investigative Committee, in April, according to the Washington Post. "So interest in his past grew and the process of bringing him out in the open naturally sped up."President Putin's spokesman, Dmitry Peskov, told CNN that Putin had not followed Navalny's trial.So then why has he been released?When Navalny arrived in court the day after his conviction, he found the prosecutor who had argued he should be sent to prison arguing instead for his release pending appeal, so that he could continue campaigning for the Moscow mayoralty.Navalny quipped that the court needed to establish the identity of the prosecutor because he may have been replaced by a double.Lipman described Navalny's release as an "amazing twist."She said that his release was unlikely to have been as a result of protest action after the verdict was announced. The protest hadn't been nationwide and involved just a few thousand people, she said."It was not enough to force the authorities to retreat. Also, the prosecutors' request that he be released ... was filed even before there was a big crowd in the streets. It's really hard to believe."It could be the result of some sort of intrigue -- rivalries, tensions at the very top of the Russian political elite."But she said any political involvement would be denied by the government.MORE: Putin defends record on freedom of speech"Their response, invariably, is, it's up to the court to decide," she said. "Of course they would never admit how they interfere."RIA Novosti reported that the trial judge "repeatedly rejected claims over his partiality and denied several motions to have him replaced."Will the conviction affect his bid to become mayor of Moscow?Lipman said that if Navalny's conviction was upheld by a higher court, his name would be unable to appear on an electoral ballot. However, she said he could campaign in the meantime."After his release yesterday he can continue running. The idea is that now he is at large up until his lawyers send in an appeal in a higher court re-examine his case. He remains at large and his verdict is not effective," she said.She said there was "good reason to predict" that the high court would uphold the verdict before the end of the campaign for the September 8 election."He is still on a hook. In a theory, this higher court could make a ruling even earlier and effectively terminate his campaign."Speaking to reporters outside court after he was released, Navalny said he would return to Moscow to discuss his next steps with his staff, RIA Novosti said."Regarding my participation in the elections, I am not some kind of a kitten or a puppy to whom they first say it can't participate in the elections and then they say, 'let's release him for a while so he can participate in the elections,'" he said.Once in Moscow, he will decide whether to boycott the election or continue his campaign, he said, according to the news agency."We'll discuss it with the staff and with the volunteers. For now, I will stay a candidate, I am not retreating."How has Navalny's conviction been received in Russia?Lipman said Navalny's conviction was not likely to cost Putin any support."I don't think it will affect his standing in the eyes of the conservative majority. The status quo is suspicious of any troublemaker," she said."The minority of more modernized urban Russians -- people who resent the government for being lawless -- people likely to sympathise with Navalny -- I think they will be even angrier."The rift between them and the government will become even broader, but we are talking about a minority."What about the rest of the world?The day Navalny was convicted, the European Union's top diplomat, Catherine Ashton, called the trial a sham. And former Soviet leader Mikhail Gorbachev issued a statement saying the case "unfortunately confirms that we do not have an independent judiciary."Rachel Denber, deputy director of Human Rights Watch's Europe and Central Asia division, said she was not surprised by the guilty verdict but was shocked by the five-year prison sentence."Navalny's prosecution is meant to silence a leader and messenger," she said.Amnesty International's Europe and Central Asia program director, John Dalhuisen, said, "This was a parody of a prosecution and a parody of a trial. The case was twice closed for lack of evidence of a crime, before being reopened on the personal instruction of Russia's top investigator."But Lipman pointed out the world had also expressed outrage over Russia's crackdown on protesters in 2011 and 2012."I don't think it has an effect. Not on previous occasions and not this time."</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130718173343-pyotr-verzilov-pussy-riot-husband---s015108556-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130719124202-exp-pavel-khodorkovsky-navalny-verdict-00011818-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120612034716-moscow-5-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120302050334-black-russia-elex-opposition-00013205-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111207091428-pkg-chance-russia-social-media-00000309-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190546im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1387590">
        <title>Hundreds of migrants rescued as Italy's coast guard averts ship crash</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/europe/italy-migrant-vessel/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Italy's coast guard says there were 796 migrants aboard the ship</highlights>
        <highlights>The crew had abandoned the freighter, which was cruising toward the rocky coast</highlights>
        <highlights>Italian coast guard brought the freighter packed with migrants safely into port</highlights>
        <highlights>The coast guard says its action saved lives, prevented an environmental disaster</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T10:40:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Livia Borghese, CNN</author>
        <content>Rome (CNN) -- It could have been, in the words of the Italian coast guard, a disaster.But thanks to authorities, a ship on course to crash against the rocky Italian coast was stopped in time, saving passengers and averting a possible environmental catastrophe.Italian coast guard commander Filippo Marini said the vessel was cruising on autopilot toward the coast at 6 nautical miles per hour. When it entered Italian search and rescue waters, the coast guard sent helicopters with six men, who boarded the ship and took control.The course of the vessel was reversed to avoid a collision with the rocks, and it was piloted instead to Gallipoli, in Italy's southern Puglia region. It docked safely there Wednesday.The freighter carried 796 migrants, the coast guard said Thursday, most believed to be from war-torn Syria. Authorities on Wednesday put the number of migrants on board at 768.The crew of the Blue Sky M apparently jumped ship.The coast guard said a collision would not only have led to the deaths of passengers, but would also have created an environmental disaster. It said a "real disaster" was avoided.The freighter sent a distress signal near the Greek island of Corfu on Tuesday, alerting Italian and Greek authorities to the situation on board.The Greek Merchant Marine Ministry and the Greek Navy have said the pilot of a Greek helicopter that flew over the cargo ship spoke with the captain, who said the ship was not in distress and did not need assistance.Floriana Segreto, a spokeswoman for the Italian coast guard in Rome, said there were no deaths related to the Blue Sky M incident. She added that about 100 people have been hospitalized, mainly because of the cold and exhaustion.It was not immediately clear where the migrants will go.The authorities will investigate what happened to the crew and how the freighter reached Italy's waters.</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1388551">
        <title>Barcelona ready to hit back after transfer ban appeal fails</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/sport/barcelona-hit-with-transfer-ban/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>Barcelona's appeal against transfer ban dismissed by Court of Arbitration of Sport</highlights>
        <highlights>Club found guilty of breaching FIFA rules on the transfer of players under 18</highlights>
        <highlights>Barcelona says it could make fresh appeal</highlights>
        <highlights>Club was initially hit with ban in April which was suspended pending two appeals</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T14:45:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Barcelona says the transfer ban placed on the club is "disproportionate" and "excessive."The Catalan club hit back on Tuesday after losing its appeal to the Court of Arbitration of Sport (CAS) following the decision to ban it from being able to sign new players over the next 12 months.CAS stated that Barcelona was guilty of breaching FIFA rules on signing minors and confirmed that the club would be unable to add to its squad during the next two transfer windows."The Panel found in particular that FC Barcelona had breached the rules regarding the protection of minors and the registration of minors attending football academies. Accordingly, the FIFA decision is confirmed in full and the sanction remains in force," a CAS statement read.FC Barcelona statement regarding CAS verdict http://t.co/vTzfdsbl5p pic.twitter.com/hScbDyzFaDBarcelona, which was also fined $455,000, said it "totally disagrees" with the verdict and will now study the different legal options at its disposal including the Swiss Federal Courts.Read: Barcelona hit with transfer ban by FIFAIn a statement, Barcelona said that it "understands and supports the policy on the protection of minors and the concern for the protection of their development and education."It added: "This is confirmed by how the club has acted throughout its history, setting an example around the world for the way its young footballers are schooled and educated, and the work that is done on their development. FC Barcelona's youth structure has enabled hundreds of young players to achieve their dreams and receive a decent upbringing."The errors that the club might have committed, and which have been recognized and argued before the corresponding authorities are, in all cases, of an administrative nature and to a large extent have been caused by the existing conflict between the FIFA regulations and Spanish legislation, along with the club's conviction that it was acting correctly."Therefore, FC Barcelona considers the sanction to be completely disproportionate as it supposes an excessive punishment for the club, when considering its trajectory and the circumstances of this specific case."Barcelona has one of the most famous and successful academies in the game with young players from all over the world learning their trade with the club."La Masia" as it is known, has helped produced talents such as Lionel Messi, who arrived from Argentina at the age of 11.The ruling comes after an investigation found the club had broken regulations regarding the transfer of young players from outside Spain.FIFA's investigation focused on several players aged under 18 who were registered and played for the club between 2009 and 2013.Under FIFA laws, clubs are not allowed to sign international players under the age of 18 unless the player is moving within the European Union, is aged between 16 and 18 and moving with their parents or the club and the player both live within 50 kilometers of a shared national border.Barcelona was originally handed a 14-month ban in April but launched an appeal to FIFA, world football's governing body which was rejected in August.But the decision to appeal to CAS meant Barcelona was allowed to complete a number of signings in the intervening period.Barcelona splashed out a reported $128.5 million to sign Uruguay international Luis Suarez from Liverpool.Belgian defender Thomas Vermaelen was brought in from Arsenal for $30m while French defender Jeremy Mathieu and Chilean goalkeeper Claudio Bravo also arrived at Camp Nou.Croatian midfielder Ivan Rakitic from Sevilla joined Barca for a fee of $23.9m with the club also paying $3m to Dinamo Zagreb for Alen Halilovic.Luis Enrique's side currently sits second in La Liga, one point behind fierce rival Real Madrid.Read: Barcelona's appeal against transfer ban rejected</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141125211304-messi-ucl-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140711132710-suarez-barcelona-image-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140403175535-exp-barca-fifa-legal-opinion-00002221-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140123160223-rosell-presser-jan-23-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216100552-henry-new-york-laughing-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605114319-eibar-gal-9-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017152545-gallery-real-madrid-refurb-6-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141027022422-bpr-south-african-soccor-senzo-meyiwa-death-00000402-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020180630-roma-centurion-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020132745-kreshnik-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017150734-ched-evans-smiling-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016105457-lionel-messi-opener-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122943-inter-milan-fan-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013170740-martin-odegaard-norway-debut-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010121745-indian-football-league-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002124314-davies-intv-rio-ferdinand-racism-00002712-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190601im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908152849-odegaard-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1389500">
        <title>All passengers off Adriatic ferry; investigation begins</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/28/world/europe/ferry-fire-italy-greece/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>Death toll rises to 10 after fire on ferry in Adriatic Sea</highlights>
        <highlights>All passengers evacuated; ship's commander leaves vessel</highlights>
        <highlights>More than 400 people had been on board stricken vessel</highlights>
        <highlights>Fire broke out early Sunday morning as ferry traveled from Greece to Italy</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T01:15:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Nima Elbagir, Dana Ford and Barbie Nadeau, CNN</author>
        <content>Brindisi, Italy (CNN) -- Conditions for the rescue of passengers off a ferry that caught fire in the Adriatic Sea could hardly have been worse.Strong winds, choppy seas and thick smoke pounded the efforts.In the end, at least 10 people died, the Italian coast guard said on Monday. But many more were saved -- 427 -- the coast guard said.Ute Kilger was one of those who survived."We were wet and cold, and the rain was like needles," she said. "There was always these explosions and this feeling you have in your feet. It goes through your body."Talking to CNN in donated Red Cross pajamas, she stumbled over her words: "It was unreal, but I knew it is so real. This was really bad, to really know, it is real."The Italian coast guard earlier said that all remaining passengers had been evacuated from the vessel, with the boat's commander finally leaving the ship at 2:50 p.m. Monday. The coast guard said it was inspecting the ship and deciding how to transport it -- and where.The public prosecutor in Bari, Italy, said he had requested the seizure of the ship as part of a criminal investigation. Authorities are waiting for authorization from Albanian officials to release the ship, because it is in Albanian waters.Giuseppe Volpe, the prosecutor, added that the owner and the captain of the ship will be notified of the investigation. No charges have been filed.More than 400 passengers were traveling on the Norman Atlantic between the Greek port of Igoumenitsa and the Italian port of Ancona when the fire began, apparently in the ferry's parking bay.'Dying of cold'In the first three hours of the fire, around 150 people were able to escape via the vessel's lifeboats. But when the ferry lost power, the electronic arms were unable to function, leaving the rest of the boats dangling uselessly by its side.After waiting for hours in rough conditions, one Greek man told Italian state broadcaster RAI TV that passengers were "dying of cold and suffocating from the smoke," and that their feet were burning from the heat of the flames.Helicopters with night vision equipment worked through the night to pull passengers off the ferry, one by one.An Italian navy medical team boarded the ship to aid passengers, some of whom had been suffering hypothermia and smoke inhalation, the navy said. The already cold conditions were worsened by the spray from tugboat hoses as authorities attempted to douse the flames.A freighter carrying 49 rescued passengers arrived at the port of Bari on Monday. Photos showed survivors wrapped in emergency foil blankets being carried away on stretchers.One man died after he jumped or fell into the cold water, authorities said. It is unclear how the other victims died.'Prisoners on a burning ship'Dramatic cell phone images filmed by a passenger showed flames through shattered portholes, while a wider view released by rescuers showed a huge plume of thick, black smoke streaming from the stricken vessel.Many passengers were unable to reach the lower decks because of the heat, and the water below was so cold that jumping clear of the ferry was not an option.Sea surface temperatures had been around 14 to 15 degrees Celsius (57 to 59 degrees Fahrenheit), CNN meteorologist Tom Sater said, which would have limited the survival time in the water to six hours at most.Passengers told Greek and Italian newsgroups they had felt like "prisoners on a burning ship."It's not known how the fire started, but it is believed to have originated in the parking bay. A truck driver told the Greek news media that trucks filled with oil were "packed like sardines," their cargo scraping the ceiling, which could have set off sparks in rough seas to start a fire, he surmised.Greek authorities said the vessel's fire doors appeared to have failed, which allowed the flames to spread quickly.More on major ferry sinkingsCNN's Nima Elbagir reported this story from Brindisi, Italy. CNN's Dana Ford wrote from Atlanta. Journalist Barbie Nadeau reported this story from Rome.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229110505-ferry-map-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229110505-ferry-map-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070012-02-italy-ferry-1229-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229035724-vo-burning-ferry-passengers-arrive-00001003-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229065736-01-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070012-02-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229102114-05-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070123-03-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228083902-greece-ferry-fire-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070307-04-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124610-06-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228182947-10-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124656-07-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228122906-03-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124200-04-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228103443-02-ferry-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229065736-01-italy-ferry-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070012-02-italy-ferry-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229102114-05-italy-ferry-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070123-03-italy-ferry-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228083902-greece-ferry-fire-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229070307-04-italy-ferry-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124610-06-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228182947-10-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124656-07-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228122906-03-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228124200-04-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228103443-02-ferry-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229065736-01-italy-ferry-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228185502-orig-natpkg-ferry-fire-adriatic-sea-00003720-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228154149-segment-ferry-fire-adriatic-sea-00001430-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228083902-greece-ferry-fire-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190602im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1392278">
        <title>Scottish woman tests negative for Ebola; patient with virus moved to London</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/europe/uk-ebola/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Woman in the Scottish Highlands tests negative for Ebola, government says</highlights>
        <highlights>A health care worker diagnosed with the virus is moved to a London hospital</highlights>
        <highlights>She was working with Save the Children in Sierra Leone as a volunteer nurse</highlights>
        <highlights>A third suspected Ebola case is being tested in the southwest of England, officials say</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T02:09:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Laura Smith-Spark, Nic Robertson and Alexander Felton, CNN</author>
        <content>London (CNN) -- A woman in the Northwest Highlands of Scotland who'd fallen ill tested negative for Ebola, the Scottish government said Tuesday.A spokesman for the government said the woman had been in West Africa recently, though she had no direct contact with anyone with Ebola."A patient at Aberdeen Royal Infirmary has tested negative for Ebola," the press release said. "The individual was transferred to the hospital by the Scottish Ambulance Service yesterday after falling ill while visiting Torridon in the Scottish Highlands."Meanwhile, a health care worker who was diagnosed with the Ebola virus after returning to Scotland from Sierra Leone was transferred to the Royal Free Hospital in London.The patient is Pauline Cafferkey, 39, of Glasgow, Scotland, the hospital said. She was working with Save the Children at an Ebola treatment center, said Michael von Bertele, humanitarian director at that organization.She traveled via Casablanca, Morocco, and London Heathrow Airport before arriving at Glasgow Airport on a British Airways flight late Sunday, the health agency NHS Scotland said.After feeling unwell, she sought medical attention and became the first person to be diagnosed with Ebola within the United Kingdom.British media outlets said Cafferkey is a public health nurse in Scotland's South Lanarkshire area who was part of a 30-strong team of medical volunteers deployed to West Africa by the UK government last month in a joint endeavor with Save the Children.She was reportedly transferred to London in a military aircraft fitted with an isolation pod.The Royal Free Hospital is equipped with a high-level isolation unit, with access restricted to specially trained medical staff. A specially designed tent, with controlled ventilation, is set up over the patient's bed.A British volunteer nurse, William Pooley, was successfully treated in the unit after he was brought home from Sierra Leone in August, having been diagnosed with Ebola there.'Extremely low' riskUK authorities are working to trace those who have come into contact with Cafferkey.The Scottish government has set up a special number for people to call if they traveled on the same London Heathrow-to-Glasgow flight as Cafferkey.British Airways said it was working closely with health authorities in England and Scotland and would help with any information needed."The safety and security of our customers and crew is always our top priority and the risk to people on board that individual flight is extremely low," the airline said.Ebola patients become infectious only after they display symptoms, such as fever and vomiting. The deadly virus is spread through contact with bodily fluids.A Downing Street spokesman told CNN that British Prime Minister David Cameron and Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon had discussed the procedures in place to handle such a case."They agreed that both governments would remain in close touch and ensure everything possible was done to support the patient and, although the risk to the general population remained low, all measures would be taken to protect public health."Possible caseAnother suspected Ebola case is being tested in southwest England at the Royal Cornwall Hospital, health officials said."We do not expect the results to be known for at least 24 hours and in the meantime the patient is being looked after in isolation, following nationally agreed guidelines and protocols to protect the health of our staff and other patients," said a joint statement from the hospital and Public Health England, a government agency.According to UK government guidelines, humanitarian workers returning from Ebola-affected countries in West Africa who've been at high risk of exposure are expected to monitor their own health for 21 days after they get home.As of December 24, at least 7,693 people had died in the current Ebola outbreak, centered in Liberia, Sierra Leone and Guinea, the World Health Organization said. There have been at least 19,695 cases.CNN's Bharati Naik contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140801152641-pkg-soares-uk-london-ebola-preps-00000905-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175823-tsr-dnt-johns-cdc-scare-00000612-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210100917-nr-time-person-of-the-year-2014-ebola-00000829-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010140326-01-ebola-liberia-1010-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141104111536-ebola-restrictions-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141028065645-emile-ouamouno-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141009182112-this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-still-from-graphic-package-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141024150658-holmes-race-for-ebola-vaccine-00003921-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012125025-ebola-virus-structure-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006091841-03-ebola-1006-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017013751-pkg-simon-risk-of-ebola-on-plane-00001919-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141019151035-spain-ebola-tests-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141015170302-01-ebola-1015-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020004450-pkg-elbagir-ebola-orphans-00021929-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013174627-cdc-ebola-guidelines-lead-gfx-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008115210-excalibur-ebola-dog-victim-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014015016-pkg-tomkins-ebola-protective-gear-00005610-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141001224002-texas-health-presbyterian-hospital-dallas-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140728125203-04-ebola-guinea-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190638im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140327172929-who-officials-ebola-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1396346">
        <title>Jules Bianchi still unconscious as he begins rehabilitation program</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180732/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/sport/jules-bianchi-latest/index.html?hpt=ieu_c2</url>
        <highlights>Jules Bianchi remains unconscious in French hospital</highlights>
        <highlights>Family says Formula One driver has started rehab</highlights>
        <highlights>Frenchman sustained a diffuse axonal injury at Japanese Grand Prix</highlights>
        <highlights>Injury suffered in October following collision on wet track</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T18:25:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Jules Bianchi remains unconscious in a French hospital following his horrific crash at October's Japanese Grand Prix, but the Formula One driver has begun a program of rehabilitation therapy, according to a statement released by his family on Tuesday.Bianchi, who suffered a head injury while driving for the now defunct Marussia team, skidded off the track in wet conditions and collided with a recovery vehicle.The Frenchman sustained a "diffuse axonal injury" which causes widespread tearing of nerve fibers across the whole of the brain, according to UK brain charity, Headway.He returned to France last month and was treated at the intensive care unit of Le Centre Hospitalier Universitaire de Nice (CHU) before moving on to the rehabilitation center."As we reach the conclusion of a difficult year for our family, we wanted to take this opportunity to provide a further update regarding Jules' medical situation, per our pledge to communicate continued information, when appropriate, to his many fans," said the driver's parents, Philippe and Christine in a statement."It was a significant and very comforting step for us to be able to bring Jules home to France last month, to continue his rehabilitation surrounded by his family and friends. This is very important for Jules and also for us."Jules' neurological status remains unchanged; he is unconscious but able to breathe unaided. Whilst there is no significant information to report, we take a great deal of comfort from the fact that Jules continues to fight, as we knew he would, and this has enabled the medical professionals caring for him to commence the planned, but very painstaking, program of rehabilitation therapy."Read: Bianchi suffers 'severe head injury'Bianchi's parents say they will continue to provide updates of their son's progress and thanked the public for their ongoing support.The statement added: "As we reflect on the events of the past few months, we would like to acknowledge once again the overwhelming warmth and affection shown towards our son. These continue to be challenging times for our family, but the knowledge that he has touched the lives of so many people all around the world has helped us through."As we come to the end of this year, my thoughts &amp; prayers remain with Jules-teammate, competitor &amp; friend #ForzaJules pic.twitter.com/T6OkEDzlyfEarlier this month, the FIA published a report which stated that Bianchi "did not slow sufficiently to avoid losing control" during his crash at the Suzuka circuit.Bianchi's Marussia team folded in November after administrators failed to find fresh investment.In the days after the crash, Marussia moved to address accusations that Bianchi had not reduced his speed and that the team had actively encouraged him not to do so."The Marussia F1 Team is shocked and angered by these allegations," said the statement issued in October."At a time when its driver is critically ill in hospital, and the team has made clear that its highest priority is consideration for Jules and his family, it is distressed to have to respond to deeply upsetting rumors and inaccuracies in respect of the circumstances of Jules' accident."Regarding point 1, Jules did slow down under the double waved yellow flags. That is an irrefutable fact, as proven by the telemetry data, which the team has provided to the FIA."Regarding point 2, an audio copy of the full radio transmission between Jules and the team, and a written transcript, were provided to the FIA."It is quite clear from the transmission and the transcript that at no point during the period leading up to Jules' accident did the team urge Jules to drive faster or make any comments suggesting that he should do so."The update on the French driver's condition comes a day after the first anniversary of Michael Schumacher's skiing accident.The seven-time world champion is continuing his recovery from the severe head injuries sustained in a crash at the French ski resort of Meribel on 29th December last year.Schumacher spent nine months in hospital in France following emergency brain surgery but was moved to the family home near Lake Geneva in Switzerland in September to continue his rehabilitation.While the German's family declined to give an update on his condition, Formula One drivers and fans expressed their continuing support for the stricken driver on social media.It has been one year already... #KeepFightingMichael our thougts are still with you and your family pic.twitter.com/j6qJxa3QZgRead: Marussia reject crash claimsRead: Schumacher urged to keep fighting</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007155950-jules-bianchi-profile-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005063036-jules-bianchi3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005082852-bianchio-sutil-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008111842-maurssia-sochi-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012165150-drivers-bianchi-tribute-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012211521-marussia-tribute-russia-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141007155950-jules-bianchi-profile-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005063036-jules-bianchi3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005082852-bianchio-sutil-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008111842-maurssia-sochi-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012165150-drivers-bianchi-tribute-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012211521-marussia-tribute-russia-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008054155-ws-jules-bianchi-f1-injury-update-00002413-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006065256-ws-jules-bianchi-injured-japan-typhoon-00002228-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006114738-bianchi-marussia-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005063036-jules-bianchi3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005053214-jules-bianchi-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005082852-bianchio-sutil-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005081705-bianchi-podium-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006114738-bianchi-marussia-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005063036-jules-bianchi3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005053214-jules-bianchi-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005082852-bianchio-sutil-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141005081705-bianchi-podium-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006114738-bianchi-marussia-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132451-sochi-bianchi-car-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132353-sochi-marussia-chilton-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131756-sochi-rosberg-bianchi-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132051-sochi-lewis-hamilton-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131509-sochi-hamilton-fairground-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131640-sochi-vettel-ecclestone-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132213-sochi-alonso-circuit-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131346-sochi-raikkonen-cycling-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132451-sochi-bianchi-car-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132353-sochi-marussia-chilton-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131756-sochi-rosberg-bianchi-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132051-sochi-lewis-hamilton-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131509-sochi-hamilton-fairground-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131640-sochi-vettel-ecclestone-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132213-sochi-alonso-circuit-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010131346-sochi-raikkonen-cycling-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010132451-sochi-bianchi-car-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212131116-marussia-f1-car-for-sale-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212131650-marussia-wheels-for-sale-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212132311-marussia-race-suit-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212132647-marussia-exhausts-for-sale-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133123-jules-bianchi-print-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133642-marussia-model-part-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133944-marussia-pit-crew-overalls-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134226-marussia-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134600-marussia-steering-wheel-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134913-marussia-team-caps-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212131116-marussia-f1-car-for-sale-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212131650-marussia-wheels-for-sale-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212132311-marussia-race-suit-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212132647-marussia-exhausts-for-sale-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133123-jules-bianchi-print-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133642-marussia-model-part-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212133944-marussia-pit-crew-overalls-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134226-marussia-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134600-marussia-steering-wheel-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212134913-marussia-team-caps-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141212131116-marussia-f1-car-for-sale-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123163938-lewis-hamilton-profile-win-2014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140316032955-grand-prix-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140417183625-lewis-hamilton-helmet-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140406174608-rosberg-hamilton-mercedes-bahrain-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140421173759-28-what-a-shot-0422-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140511140206-lewis-hamilton-spanish-grand-prix-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140526160315-20-what-a-shot-0526-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140609171155-35-what-a-shot-0609-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140622180144-rosberg-austria-team-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140707152218-19-what-a-shot-0708-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140725125242-rosberg-hungary-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140720110859-rosberg-leads-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140828174115-mercedes-spa-clash-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119172053-hamilton-italy-win-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119171720-rosberg-hamilton-singapore-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119171221-rosberg-hamilton-japan-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119173333-hamilton-russia-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119173950-lewis-hamilton-fans-austin-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119175207-rosberg-brazil-win-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123163040-lewis-flag-abu-dhabi-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123163938-lewis-hamilton-profile-win-2014-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140316032955-grand-prix-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140417183625-lewis-hamilton-helmet-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140406174608-rosberg-hamilton-mercedes-bahrain-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140421173759-28-what-a-shot-0422-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140511140206-lewis-hamilton-spanish-grand-prix-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140526160315-20-what-a-shot-0526-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140609171155-35-what-a-shot-0609-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140622180144-rosberg-austria-team-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140707152218-19-what-a-shot-0708-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140725125242-rosberg-hungary-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140720110859-rosberg-leads-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140828174115-mercedes-spa-clash-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119172053-hamilton-italy-win-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119171720-rosberg-hamilton-singapore-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119171221-rosberg-hamilton-japan-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119173333-hamilton-russia-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119173950-lewis-hamilton-fans-austin-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141119175207-rosberg-brazil-win-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123163040-lewis-flag-abu-dhabi-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123163938-lewis-hamilton-profile-win-2014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140417183625-lewis-hamilton-helmet-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141106115619-f1-smoke-toro-rosso-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141107140155-spc-circuit-f1-sponsorship-administration-00020614-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140923172238-kimi-raikkonen-sunglasses-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141012183712-marc-marquez-wins-2014-title-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008174143-danni-kyvat-profile-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140918112639-jb-enviro-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140905125252-rosberg-hamilton-split-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140801103720-ricciardo-champagne-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722101410-pasta-f1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140701191650-schumacher-thoughtful-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102190650im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140523124151-monaco-grid-girls-2012-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
</ns2:topic>
