<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns2:topic xmlns:ns2="http://schema/" topicid="1398007">
    <topicname>Latin America</topicname>
    <news newsid="1399233">
        <title>U.S. condemns Cuba's reported arrest of 6 dissidents</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/americas/us-cuba-dissident-arrests/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>The United States and Cuba exchanged prisoners two weeks ago</highlights>
        <highlights>The move was part of a change in U.S. policy toward the island nation</highlights>
        <highlights>Dissidents reported several arrests ahead of a planned rally Tuesday</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T16:59:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Patrick Oppmann and Karl Penhaul, CNN</author>
        <content>Havana, Cuba (CNN) -- Two weeks after the United States and Cuba agreed to thaw decades of icy relations, the U.S. State Department blasted the Cuban government for reportedly arresting at least six dissidents.There was no comment from Cuban authorities on the arrests that were reported by other dissidents and the U.S. State Department."We are deeply concerned about the latest reports of detentions and arrests by Cuban authorities of peaceful civil society members and activists," State Department spokesman Jeff Rathke said in a statement.Roberta Jacobson, the assistant secretary of state for Western Hemisphere Affairs, wrote Tuesday on Twitter that "Freedom of expression remains core of U.S. policy on ‪Cuba, we support activists exercising those rights and condemn today's detentions."Jacobson is expected to travel to Havana in January to lead U.S. efforts to normalize relations with Cuba, U.S. government officials had previously said.The reported detentions came after a Cuban performance artist called for an open forum to demand changes from the country's single-party communist government.The event was due to take place in Havana's revolution square, the central plaza usually reserved for speeches from Fidel and Raul Castro and visiting dignitaries like Pope John Paul II.Cuban dissidents said the artist, Tania Bruguera, well-known for pushing the limits of freedom of expression in Cuba, was also arrested before the protest could begin.Bruguera had tried to convince Cuban officials to allow the event to go forward but on Tuesday the government-run union for artists and writers released a statement calling her proposal a "political provocation" meant to derail improving U.S.-Cuban relations.Government critic and blogger Yoani Sanchez wrote that she supported the event but on Tuesday tweeted that she was under house arrest and her husband had been taken away by police.CNN saw a police car and two uniformed police officers, as well as at least two men in civilian clothes who appeared to be security agents, outside the building where Sanchez lives on Tuesday. No one answered her door when the CNN crew tried to reach her for comment.Cubans have limited access to the Internet and despite a social media campaign to raise awareness about the event, the protest never materialized Tuesday.On December 17, Cuba released U.S. contractor Alan Gross, who'd been held since 2009 for smuggling satellite equipment onto the island. His freedom was part of a landmark deal paving the way for a major overhaul in U.S. policy toward Cuba.Cuba also freed a Cuban double agent who had worked as a U.S. intelligence source and who'd been held for more than 20 years, although authorities did not identify that person for security reasons. For its part, the United States released three of five Cuban intelligence agents convicted of espionage in 2001.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231104754-01-cuba-dissidents-1231-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141227153042-exp-will-cuba-loosen-its-grip-on-press-00002001-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217175614-tl-alan-gross-reunion-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220144946-nr-cuba-obama-debate-00010801-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141219141020-obama-speech-1219-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217090440-alan-gross-file-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217113524-alan-gross-arrival-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217093119-downtown-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217102439-obama-castro-split-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111007033010-cuban-five-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023142-02-cuban-missile-1015-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141202102201-2016-republicans-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218000425-perez-obama-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141128130939-cuba-flag-car-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130928163118-yasiel-puig-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141205115137-vatican-pope-audience-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120711080942-little-havana-dominoes-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140611101328-alan-gross-us-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035953im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217092848-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1401853">
        <title>Generation gap: Renewed ties expose painful Cuban-American rift</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/27/world/americas/cuban-american-generation-gap/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>Differences between new, older generations shape politics behind historic change</highlights>
        <highlights>Raul Moas, 26, finds painful silence from relatives when he tells them of visiting Cuba</highlights>
        <highlights>Cuban-American exile, 68, says "the new generation did not suffer what we did"</highlights>
        <highlights>"There is a tremendous generational divide," pollster says of latest survey</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-27T22:52:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Michael Martinez and Jaqueline Hurtado, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- When Raul Moas took his first trip to Cuba, he plunged deep in the generational chasm among Cuban-Americans that now shapes much of the politics behind this month's historic renewal of U.S.-Cuba ties.Born and raised in Miami, 26-year-old Moas discovered his trip to the ancestral land in 2011 is still a taboo among his parents and grandparents forced to flee the island during a communist revolution in the 1960s.That generation made a blood pact to never return to the isle as long as brothers Fidel and Raul Castro continued their communist rule. It's amounted to 55 years and counting.So when Moas later told his family of his visit to Cuba, many relatives stood in stone silence."When I came back and had the discussion -- 'Hey, surprise, I went to Cuba!' -- my maternal grandmother was happy, but many others of my family were much more tempered and said thank you and they walked out of the room," Moas recounted."Even within my own family, there's conflicting tension. That's a microcosm of what the Cuban-American community is going through," Moas said.For decades, Cuban-Americans were a near monolithic voice in condemning the Castro regime and energizing American policies that punished and isolated Cuba.Now, a half century later, the grandchildren and children of those exiles who lost everything to the communist revolution are being credited with infusing the Cuban-American community with new viewpoints -- ones that would have been crushed by community leaders a generation ago.A divided communityIn fact, Cuban-Americans are now a divided people and are evenly split nationwide about President Barack Obama's announcement to normalize relations with Cuba, according to a new poll by the Miami Herald, Tampa Bay Times and the polling firm Bendixen &amp; Amandi International.The gap is evident by how nearly twice as many U.S.-born Cuban-Americans agree with Obama than those Cuban-Americans born in Cuba, according to the poll, taken immediately after Obama's announcement.In effect, there are now two Cuban-American communities, said Fernand Amandi, managing partner of the polling firm.The poll found how 67% of those aged 65 and older disagree with Obama's normalizing of relations, but 52% of Cuban-Americans under age 65 support it."There is a tremendous generational divide," said Amandi, who's been polling the community for 30 years.Past attacks on dissentIt wasn't too long ago when the community solidly supported U.S. sanctions against Cuba, for better or worse.In fact, condemnation of any contact with Cuba was once so strong that Americas Watch expressed alarm in a 1992 report and documented a litany of "attacks on freedom of expression in Miami's Cuban exile community." Those attacks targeted dissent from the hard line against the Castros-led Cuba.The arrival of a new generation or two has opened the community to different views about U.S. policy."For some time now, the polls have been telling us that recent arrivals from Cuba -- those who have arrived since 1990 -- and those who were born and raised in the United States, have favored the normalization of diplomatic and trade relations with Cuba," said Maria Cristina Garcia, an American studies professor at Cornell University."In turn, those who lived through the most traumatic years of the Cuban revolution are understandably more angry about the new developments. The passage of time has not healed all wounds and memories," Garcia said. "I think any person who has experienced trauma can understand why this older generation view the announcement as a type of betrayal."Many in the younger generation in south Florida are ready for a change."I represent a generation of Cubans who are very interested in the future of Cuba. We think that the best days for Cuba have yet to come. And we think that in the end, the Cuban people need to stop being pieces in a game of chess," George Davila said.An older generation betrayedEven in the unofficial Cuban-American capital of Miami, a slight majority now opposes continuing the U.S. embargo of Cuba, and a large majority favors diplomatic relations and the lifting of U.S. travel restrictions to the island, according to a 2014 poll by Florida International University.Younger Cuban-Americans support those changes in larger numbers than the older generations, the study said.Against that backdrop of changing opinions, Obama and Cuban President Raul Castro announced plans this month to exchange embassies and renew diplomatic ties for the first time since 1961.Obama also will ease parts of the U.S. embargo against Cuba. The two countries swapped prisoners in December.Though historic, the changes hardly soothe the deep psychic scars carried by many senior Cuban-Americans.Among those most traumatized by the Cuban revolution were the 14,000 unaccompanied Cuban children airlifted to the United States in a U.S.-sponsored operation called Pedro Pan, a reference to Peter Pan. Parents sent their children to U.S. soil out of fear that communism would usurp parental authority.Many children were later reunited with their parents in America, but others ended up in the care of Catholic churches, orphanages, foster homes and delinquency facilities."They don't know the Cuba I know"One of those children, Estela Bueno, now 68, called Obama's normalizing of relations with Cuba as "one of the saddest days in my life.""To see my government that is the United States would do such a thing, it does not value what they say about freedom of expression and the human rights," said Bueno, who was 15 when Operation Pedro Pan brought her to America."The new generation did not suffer what we did, they did not see what we did," Bueno said. "They don't know how the Castros are.... It's an oppression, and the new generations don't know that and they don't know the Cuba I know, and for them it's different and for them it's an advancement, but it doesn't compare what we saw."Her husband, Arturo, 69, also arrived to the United States as one of the Pedro Pans, at age 16. The couple, who met in college, lives in Torrance, California.Obama's announcement was "an insult and a betrayal," including to those Cubans who perished in the shark-infested Straits of Florida on rafts and unseaworthy boats while fleeing the island, he said."It surprised me completely," Arturo Bueno said. "It's a betrayal to the memory of many Cubans who have died and who have died in the ocean or that they've killed just because they didn't agree with the communist government."I always thought that sooner or later we would have an agreement, between the U.S. government and Cuba, but not a government under the Castro brothers," he added.Presidential politicsThe rift provides a political climate for Obama to pursue the bold change, particularly in the nation's third most populous state of Florida, where Cuban-Americans are a powerful influence on presidential races, typically in favor of Republicans, analysts say.But even that is changing, too."President Obama won Cubans in South Florida last cycle in 2012 narrowly, but he did. So there's a big generational divide in that community. And that's one of the reasons I think he feels he can make this calculation without screwing Democrats in Florida going forward," said John Avlon, a political analyst and editor-in-chief of the Daily Beast.Seeing pain, but sensing opportunityLike other young Cuban-Americans with parents from the island, Felice Gorordo of Miami treads lightly when talking about Cuba with older relatives.Visiting Cuba is even a more perilous subject.Gorordo's father left Cuba in 1961 as one of the Pedro Pans. Gorordo's mother left Cuba in the 1970s as a teenager.In 2002, Gorordo, then 19, decided to visit Cuba and see the relatives his parents left behind."My grandparents were very against it and so were my parents," said Gorordo, now 31, who runs a startup firm providing tax filing services to immigrants."You have to recognize there is a lot of pain in this community, and it's real and you can't deny it or cover it up," Gorordo added. "But at the same, there's a sentiment among younger Cuban-Americans and even the older ones that this might be an opportunity to bring about change that we hoped for in Cuba."Seeking changeThat sort of change ultimately calls for a democracy in now communist Cuba. It's a vision that Fidel and Raul Castro certainly don't share or won't allow.That doesn't deter Gorordo and his generation.Gorordo, Moas and a network of 5,000 U.S. students at 50 universities seek change in Cuba by giving their island-based contemporaries a lode of technology.They send laptops, flash drives, tablets and phones so that Cubans can better their lives and amplify their voices in "the Western Hemisphere's last dictatorship," according to the website for the U.S. student group called Roots of Hope, or Raices de Esperanza, based in Miami Beach, Florida. Moas is executive director, and Gorordo a co-founder.The group's donations align with how Obama is now allowing the export of more U.S. telecommunications and Internet equipment to Cuba, where only 5% of the population enjoys unfiltered access to the web.Revolutionary's descendant uses baseballOne member of the group, Cuban-American Luke Salas sought change by trying to become the first American to play baseball in Cuban pro leagues since 1961.Salas, 30, declined to state how his 2011-2012 quest in Cuba ended, but he's made a yet unreleased film, "Cuban Dream," about it."It got political as you can imagine," Salas said. "The State Department called me and questioned my motives and threatened to put me in jail if I kept going down there and played baseball. The Cuban side didn't know what to make of me."For me, there's no greater platform for Cubans and Americans to come together than baseball because it's a common love and national pastime."Salas' great-great uncle, Cesar Salas, was a right-hand man to Cuban national hero Jose Marti, a revolutionary who led the independence movement of the late 1800s.By 1960, however, Luke Salas's grandparents and father fled the island for the United States.It can be a painful topic for them."Of course, I understand my 94-year-old grandmother crying, and it's not her homeland any more," said Salas, who was born and raised in Los Angeles."This younger generation, the millennials, we are more in a position to see hope and we can see a younger generation in Cuba that needs help," he said.Nothing will changeOlder generation Cuban-Americans such as Oscar Pichardo, 63, of Redondo Beach, California, call Obama's diplomatic and trade initiative with Cuba "a major insult and a slap in the face," he said.Pichardo recalled how parents sent him and others to the United States when the Castro regime sought to conscript youngsters in the military."My parents left everything behind, absolutely everything," said Pichardo, who reunited with his parents in the United States a year after he was airlifted during Operation Pedro Pan.With his long view of Cuba, Pichardo contends that, in the end, Obama's measures won't change a thing in Cuba.He pointed to how nothing changed on the island after the late Pope John Paul II visited the island in 1998 at the invitation of then-President Fidel Castro, now 88.The Pope publicly urged freedom there in what was the first papal visit in Cuban history."I think in five years we will be here and we are going to look at this day and say nothing has changed," Pichardo said. "Remember, the same promises that (Raul) Castro is telling Obama, (Fidel Castro) said 15 to 20 years ago to the Pope, and nothing changed in the 20 years since the Pope went to Cuba."So history is repeating itself," Pichardo asserted.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153738-07-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223151722-01-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223151940-01-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153059-04-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223152347-02-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223152906-03-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153232-05-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153405-06-bueno-family-122314-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153738-07-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223151722-01-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223151940-01-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153059-04-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223152347-02-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223152906-03-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153232-05-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141223153405-06-bueno-family-122314-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220143819-young-cuban-americans-optimistic-about-new-relations-with-cuba-00011513-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141219212132-exp-gps-1215-take-cuba-embargo-00004726-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141219083243-cnnee-pkg-alexandrino-pr-reax-to-cuba-usa-relations-00021409-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220144946-nr-cuba-obama-debate-00010801-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220033716-pkg-flores-cuba-reaction-to-obama-00015417-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141221043326-pkg-flores-cuba-winners-losers-00011703-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220195623-pichardo-photos-story-body.jpeg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191216im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141220154611-pichardo-passport-story-body.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1402882">
        <title>Joe Manganiello and Sofia Vergara reportedly engaged</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/showbiz/celebrity-news-gossip/feat-joe-manganiello-sofia-vergara-engaged/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>"Magic Mike" star Manganiello reportedly proposed on Christmas Day</highlights>
        <highlights>The pair have been dating for six months</highlights>
        <highlights>He told People she is "just gorgeous"</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T12:54:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Lisa Respers France, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- One of Hollywood's most attractive couples is heading down the aisle.According to People, Joe Manganiello and Sofia Vergara are engaged. The "True Blood" star reportedly asked the "Modern Family" star to marry him on Christmas Day while the pair vacationed in Hawaii.The couple have been relatively low-profile, as celebs go, during their six months of dating. They are said to have met in May during the White House Correspondents' Dinner. At the time, Vergara was still with ex-fiance Nick Loeb.By July, Manganiello and Vergara were being seen together, and he told People she was his celebrity crush: "She's got the curves; she's got a beautiful face, beautiful hair, just gorgeous."Happy happy bday to my love and best friend ❤️❤️to the one that makes me laugh like crazy!have a healthy wonderfull year babe!!!@joemanganielloA photo posted by Sofia Vergara (@sofiavergara) on Dec 12, 2014 at 9:51am PSTOn Sunday, Vergara wished her love happy birthday on her Instagram account with a picture of them and a caption that read "Happy happy bday to my love and best friend to the one that makes me laugh like crazy!have a healthy wonderfull year babe!!!"Neither has commented on reports of the engagement.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230080945-sofia-vergara-and-manganiello-gq-party-2014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130603155622-kanye-west-kim-kardashian-angel-ball-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022090929-celeb-engagements-heidi-klum-seal-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022090723-celeb-engagements-jason-sehorn-angie-harmon-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130213100129-power-couples-mariah-carey-and-nick-cannon-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022095932-celeb-engagements-nick-cannon-selita-ebansk-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022101439-celeb-engagements-ashley-tisdale-christopher-french-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022102648-celeb-engagements-ace-young-diana-degarmo-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121008072332-splits-katie-holmes-and-tom-cruise-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022104211-celeb-engagements-katherine-heigl-josh-kelley-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111118082729-dean-mcdermott-tori-spelling-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022112730-celeb-engagements-courteney-cox-arquette-david-arquette-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120404094114-william-and-kate-engagement-announcement-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121203060827-courtney-mazza-mario-lopez-02-12-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230080945-sofia-vergara-and-manganiello-gq-party-2014-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130603155622-kanye-west-kim-kardashian-angel-ball-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022090929-celeb-engagements-heidi-klum-seal-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022090723-celeb-engagements-jason-sehorn-angie-harmon-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130213100129-power-couples-mariah-carey-and-nick-cannon-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022095932-celeb-engagements-nick-cannon-selita-ebansk-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022101439-celeb-engagements-ashley-tisdale-christopher-french-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022102648-celeb-engagements-ace-young-diana-degarmo-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121008072332-splits-katie-holmes-and-tom-cruise-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022104211-celeb-engagements-katherine-heigl-josh-kelley-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111118082729-dean-mcdermott-tori-spelling-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131022112730-celeb-engagements-courteney-cox-arquette-david-arquette-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120404094114-william-and-kate-engagement-announcement-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191231im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121203060827-courtney-mazza-mario-lopez-02-12-topics.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1404367">
        <title>IOC to tackle threat to Olympic sailors of super-bug in Rio's waters</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/23/sport/rio-olympics-sailing-super-bug/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>Researchers find an antibiotic-resistant super-bacteria in the sailing waters for the Olympics</highlights>
        <highlights>Rio officials insist the risk to sailors will be "minimal" despite the research</highlights>
        <highlights>Sailors have already complained less than two years out from the Games for its filthy waters</highlights>
        <highlights>70% of the city's sewage is spilled into the bay where the Games sailing will take place</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-23T14:28:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Matt Majendie, for CNN</author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Olympic chiefs have pledged to arrest fears that sailors and windsurfers at the next Games will not just have to deal with their rivals on the water but a potential super-bug under it.Researchers have found a bacteria more typically encountered in hospital waste which produces the enzyme KPC in several different locations along the Carioca River, which feeds Guanabara Bay where the sailing events will take place.The bacteria is resistant to antibiotics and can cause urinary, gastrointestinal and pulmonary infections although Rio officials are adamant the risk is "minimal."But the International Olympic Committee insisted it had been made aware of the problem and was working closely with Rio officials to minimize any potential risks.The IOC statement, sent to CNN, read: "The health and safety of the athletes is our number one priority. Rio has created a task force to monitor this situation and we are being kept fully updated by them."We will continue to work with Rio to ensure that the athletes are able to compete safely and in the best conditions possible."The research is the work of the Oswaldo Cruz Foundation, considered one of the world's main public health research institutions.Study coordinator Ana Paula D'Alincourt Carvalho Assef, of the foundation, said in an email to the Associated Press: "There is a risk of contracting diseases, which are not more serious than those caused by other microorganisms. The problem is that in case of infection, it is possible that treatment involves hospitalization."Since the super-bacteria are resistant to most modern medications, doctors need to rely on drugs that are rarely used because they are toxic to the organism."Earlier this year, biologist Mario Moscatelli described the Marina Gloria, which will serve as a base for the sailing competitions, as a "toilet."While Rio mayor Eduardo Paes admits a planned clean-up will not be completed prior to the Games, state officials have allayed fears over the risk to sailing competitors that take to the water.In a lengthy statement from the State Environmental Institute, forwarded to CNN, it said: "According to the president of the institute (State Environmental Institute) Isaura Frega the bacterium is not very resistant in the environment, especially in salt water."There's no need to panic. The possibility of discovering this bacteria in our beaches is minimal, almost non-existent -- assured Isaura Frega, highlighting that there are no records of people -- contaminated with the bacteria outside of the hospital environment -- being admitted to Rio de Janeiro's public hospitals."KPC is a bacteria which loses its potency when it comes into contact with salt water. It's not an aggressive bacteria. It's only resistant to antibiotics. It only represents a risk to those people who have a weak immune system -- explained the specialist."As for Rio 2016 organizers, they have been in contact both with the government and also the Oswaldo Cruz Foundation.A spokesman for Rio 2016 told CNN: "We were alerted to a possible presence of KPC-type bacteria in some parts of the Carioca River. Rio 2016 created a task force regarding this matter."The group will continue to monitor the matter very closely and discuss with the government and with specialists the solutions to prevent contamination of the water and continue to guarantee the safety of athletes. This issue does not impose any change in our planning for the test events and competition events."</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191235im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222091108-rio-sailing-super-bug-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191235im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141113150956-spc-mainsail-isaf-world-championships-a-00010626-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191235im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130110114639-mainsail-sydney-hobart-race-rio-2016-b-00014322-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191235im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130110042529-mainsail-sydney-hobart-race-rio-2016-c-00053323-story-body.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1405246">
        <title>Kidnapped Mexican priest found dead on Christmas Day</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/26/world/americas/mexico-violence/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>A priest was found shot in the head in Guerrero state on Christmas Day, his diocese says</highlights>
        <highlights>He'd been kidnapped a few days earlier by unidentified men, church officials say</highlights>
        <highlights>Guerrero State is cartel territory where 43 students went missing three months ago</highlights>
        <highlights>Priests protested on Christmas Eve with signs saying "Ya Basta" ("Enough Already")</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-27T12:57:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Elwyn Lopez and Susanna Capelouto, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- A missing priest in violence-plagued Guerrero state was found dead in an alley on Christmas Day, his diocese said.The Rev. Gregorio Lopez Gorostieta, who was forced out of his truck and kidnapped by unidentified men days before, had been shot in the head, according to the Diocese of Altamirano."We are tired of pain and delinquency, injustice and corruption," said Bishop Maximino Martinez Miranda. "We want the incidents to be clarified, as well as the death of so many people in Guerrero state. We live in a moment of violence."No suspects or motives are known."There is a moment when priests come out to reclaim justice for the people, and that perhaps does not please everyone," the bishop said. "There are many hypotheses. We are leaving this in the hands of the corresponding authorities."Guerrero is drug cartel territory. Ciudad Altamirano is about a two-hour drive from Iguala, the city where 43 students from a rural teachers college went missing three months ago.Authorities believe the students were taken by police in Iguala and turned over to gang members. The gang members killed the students, burned the bodies and dumped some of them them in a river, authorities allege.Lopez is the second priest from the diocese found dead since September.Father Ascension Acuna Osorio, whose body was found floating in a river, had been serving in a church an hour's drive from the Cathedral Altamirano. Authorities are still investigating his death, according to the diocese.On Christmas Eve, the night before Lopez's body was found and his death announced by the diocese, fellow priests had held a protest against the violence and called for his release. They carried signs that read "Ya Basta" ("Enough Already").</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1406293">
        <title>Argentine orangutan granted unprecedented legal rights</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/23/world/americas/feat-orangutan-rights-ruling/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>An animal rights group files a writ asking for freedom for Argentine orangutan Sandra</highlights>
        <highlights>Sandra had been living at the Buenos Aires Zoo for 20 years</highlights>
        <highlights>A court rules that Sandra is a "nonhuman being" with rights to freedom and "no harm"</highlights>
        <highlights>The zoo has up to two weeks to appeal the ruling</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-23T21:50:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Emiliano Giménez, Special to CNN Espanol</author>
        <content>Editor's note: Read this story in Spanish at CNN Espanol.(CNN Espanol) -- In a world first, a court in Argentina issued a historic and unprecedented ruling that favors the rights of an orangutan held in captivity. Sandra the orangutan was granted a legal action so she may be transferred to a habitat in keeping with her development.Argentina's Association of Professional Lawyers for Animal Rights filed a writ of habeas corpus, a resource to avoid arbitrary arrests, on Sandra's behalf. Once the release and transfer order is issued, the orangutan would be taken to a sanctuary in Brazil, where she would live under partial or controlled freedom.Sandra, who has been living in captivity for the past 20 years at the Buenos Aires Zoo, was considered a "nonhuman being" and she was granted basic rights, such as life, freedom and a premise of "no harm" either physically or psychologically.Argentina's Federal Chamber of Criminal Cassation ruled the primate is a subject of law, "a nonhuman being that has certain rights, and can enforce them through legal procedure," according to Andrés Gil Domínguez, Sandra's attorney."This is an unprecedented ruling, the first ruling worldwide," said the lawyer.Previously, Argentine laws interpreted animals as things.Buenos Aires Zoo officials did not issue a statement but will have up to two weeks to appeal the ruling.Even though this is a case that sets a global precedent, specialists in this matter confirmed this type of ruling only applies to cases like Sandra's and great apes, who share 96% of their genetic identity with human beings.Science considers chimpanzees, gorillas and orangutans to have understanding and feelings that can be compared with those of humans."It has been proven that Sandra and primates held in captivity have not only lost their freedom, they have lost the ability to live in a natural habitat, but it has also been proven that they are affected, that they suffer from confinement, and it is damage that is deep and serious," said Gil.Some animal rights activists interpret this ruling as opening new perspectives for species in captivity.For Pia Pacheco, from the NGO Project Gran Simio Argentina, this case is "a reflection of certain changes that are taking place in our country in matters related to the consideration people have towards animals and the future they may have."</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191248im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222165446-cnnee-gimenez-argentina-orangutan-rights-00000620-story-top.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1407979">
        <title>Cuban spy's ultimate mystery: How he got his wife pregnant from a U.S. prison</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/21/world/americas/cuban-spy-artificial-insemination/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>Gerardo Hernandez was the head of the spy ring known as the Wasp Network</highlights>
        <highlights>Since 2001, he was being held in a U.S. prison; he was released in a prisoner swap</highlights>
        <highlights>Havana has been abuzz since his wife in Cuba showed up pregnant during news coverage</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-23T00:17:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Patrick Oppmann and Evan Perez, CNN</author>
        <content>Havana, Cuba (CNN) -- It might be the most bizarre of the closely guarded secrets from last week's historic agreement between the United States and Cuba: How did the leader of a Cuban spy ring serving life in a California federal prison manage to impregnate his wife 2,245 miles away in Havana?As part of the most significant diplomatic breakthrough between the United States and Cuba in more than 50 years, a prisoner swap was made. To uphold its part of the bargain, the U.S. released three Cuban spies, including Gerardo Hernandez, the head of the spy ring known as the Wasp Network.Hernandez had an ear-to-ear smile Wednesday as he arrived at Havana's Jose Marti International Airport. State TV showed Hernandez as he was greeted by President Raul Castro and then embraced and kissed his wife, Adriana Perez.Cubans watching the nonstop coverage of the prisoner swap were shocked when the cameras zeroed in on Hernandez hugging Perez. She was obviously in the late stages of a pregnancy that had no easy explanation.Not only had Hernandez been serving a double life sentence, but his wife also worked for Cuba's intelligence services and was banned by U.S. officials from visiting her husband in prison, according to the Cuban government.Rumors swirl in sultry HavanaThe subject became the immediate hot topic in Havana where rumors swirled fast about the baby's paternity and whether the Cuban government could have somehow arranged a clandestine conjugal visit under the nose of U.S. authorities.The couple appeared at another event on Saturday, where together with the other freed spies, Castro and the communist island's top political and military officials showered them with applause.A beaming Hernandez stood by Perez, whose round stomach was clearly visible for viewers of the live broadcastAs the couple left the celebration, Hernandez hinted at the secret surrounding the pregnancy."Everyone's asking, and we have had a lot of fun with the comments and speculations. The reality is it had to be kept quiet," Hernandez told the government-run television channel. "We can't give a lot of details, because we don't want to hurt people who meant well."He said his wife's pregnancy was a direct result of the high-level talks."One of the first things accomplished by this process was this," Hernandez said, gesturing to his Perez's stomach. "I had to do it by 'remote control,' but everything turned out well."Two sources involved with the diplomatic talks, when questioned by CNN, uncloaked the mystery: During the negotiations, Hernandez's sperm was collected and sent to Cuba, where Perez was artificially inseminated.The U.S. Justice Department confirmed the story, without going into the details."We can confirm the United States facilitated Mrs. Hernandez's request to have a baby with her husband," spokesman Brian Fallon said.What the U.S. would gainWhy would the U.S. government do this? The artificial insemination was made possible in exchange for better conditions for Alan Gross, a U.S. contractor imprisoned in Cuba. Gross was released last week as part of the prisoner swap."In light of Mr. Hernandez's two life sentences," Fallon said, "the request was passed along by Senator [Patrick] Leahy, who was seeking to improve the conditions for Mr. Gross while he was imprisoned in Cuba."The discretion on both sides makes sense.For 18 months, officials from both countries refused to admit that they were even holding high-level talks.Officials communicated via back channels, knowing that any leak about the talks could doom the talks.Impregnating Perez involved cutting through bureaucratic red tape at multiple U.S. government agencies.As Perez began to show, officials from both countries fretted over how they would explain her pregnancy and what to do if the baby arrived before the talks succeeded.2001 convictionHernandez was convicted in 2001 of conspiracy to commit murder for his role in the Brothers to the Rescue shoot down that left four Cuban-Americans dead after Cuban Air Force MIGs blew up the two civilian planes as they flew toward Havana to distribute anti-government leaflets. He received two life sentences.Cuban authorities said Hernandez and the other operatives were trying to prevent terrorist attacks from being carried out on their homeland by violent Miami exiles.That the U.S. government helped a man convicted of plotting the murder of four Cuban-Americans and spying on the exile community in Miami will likely further rankle many of the same Cuban-Americans who were already furious that Washington is restoring diplomatic relations with Havana.But Tim Reiser, an aide to Leahy who worked to broker the landmark agreement with Cuba, said helping Hernandez conceive a child led to better treatment for Gross by Cuban authorities and was an important concession to help reach a historic deal."The expectation was that this man would die in prison. This was her only chance of having a child," Rieser told CNN.Gerardo Hernandez said he and his wife are expecting their baby daughter to arrive in two weeks and they will name her Gema.Patrick Oppman reported and wrote from Havana, Cuba. Evan Perez reported from Washington.</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1409369">
        <title>Sources identify mystery man freed in historic U.S.-Cuba deal</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/18/world/americas/cuba-us-agent-released/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>Sources inside the government and out tell CNN his name is Rolando Sarraff Trujillo</highlights>
        <highlights>He was released along with Alan Gross, in exchange for three convicted Cuban spies</highlights>
        <highlights>Sarraff, a Cuban national, spent two decades in prison</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-19T02:36:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Joe Johns and Dana Ford, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Upon his release from prison, he was described by President Barack Obama as "one of the most important intelligence agents that the United States has ever had in Cuba."Yet very little is known about the man.U.S. officials have refused to release the spy's name, but sources inside the government and out tell CNN his name is Rolando Sarraff Trujillo.Sarraff, a Cuban national, was part of a historic deal reached this week between the United States and Cuba. He spent two decades in prison.He was released along with Alan Gross, an American subcontractor held for five years, in exchange for three convicted Cuban spies."This man -- whose sacrifice has been known to only a few -- provided America with the information that led us to arrest the network of Cuban agents that included the men transferred to Cuba today as well as other spies in the United States," Obama said Wednesday.Who was released?Sarraff, now in his early 50s, was discovered and convicted of espionage in Cuba in 1995.According to the office of the director of national intelligence, he provided the U.S. government with information that "was instrumental in the identification and disruption of several Cuban intelligence operatives in the United States and ultimately led to ... successful federal espionage prosecutions."Specifically, the U.S. intelligence office tied Sarraff to the conviction of one-time Defense Intelligence Agency senior analyst Ana Belen Montes, who was sentenced to 25 years after pleading guilty of spying for the Cuban government in 2002.Why the Cuba deal happened nowHe's also tied to the case of ex-State Department official Walter Kendall Myers and his wife, Gwendolyn, who pleaded guilty in 2009 for illegally aiding the Cuban government for decades.Sarraff played a role in helping federal authorities go after the Florida-based Wasp Network, including members of the Cuban Five. Three of those five were released this week as part of the deal."Securing his release from prison after 20 years -- in a swap for three of the Cuban spies he helped put behind bars -- is fitting closure to this Cold World chapter of U.S.-Cuban relations," the DNI office said.The long history between the U.S. and CubaCNN's Greg Botelho and Ray Sanchez contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217090440-alan-gross-file-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217113524-alan-gross-arrival-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217093119-downtown-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217102439-obama-castro-split-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111007033010-cuban-five-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023142-02-cuban-missile-1015-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141202102201-2016-republicans-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218000425-perez-obama-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141128130939-cuba-flag-car-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130928163118-yasiel-puig-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141205115137-vatican-pope-audience-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120711080942-little-havana-dominoes-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140611101328-alan-gross-us-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191253im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217092848-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1410497">
        <title>In the waters between the U.S. and Cuba lies a long history</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180734/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/17/world/americas/cuba-u-s-relationship-history/index.html?hpt=ila_c2</url>
        <highlights>The United States helped Cuba win independence from Spain in 1898</highlights>
        <highlights>The new Republic of Cuba allows the U.S. naval base in Guantanamo in 1903</highlights>
        <highlights>U.S. comes to brink of nuclear war with Cuba and Soviet Union in 1962</highlights>
        <highlights>A custody battle over Elian Gonzalez becomes an international incident in 1999</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-18T04:05:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Michael Martinez, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Just 90 miles away, Cuba inevitably shares a long history with the United States, from conquistadors to the Spanish-American War to the Cold War.Here are some of the top moments in that history, even before the countries came into being.Old World meets New WorldChristopher Columbus lands on Cuba in 1492 and claims the island for Spain, leading the way for that country's conquistadors to explore the Caribbean and the part of the U.S. Southeast that's now Florida, among other parts of the Americas.Spanish-American WarThe United States helps Cuba win independence from Spain in a war between the European country and the Americans in 1898. In one of the more famous moments, Theodore Roosevelt and his Rough Riders charge up Cuba's Kettle Hill during the Battle of Santiago, and the so-called 1st Volunteer Cavalry become instant heroes.The United States is given temporary control of Cuba under the Treaty of Paris, and Roosevelt later becomes U.S. President.Guantanamo BayThe U.S. occupation of Cuba lasts until 1902, during which U.S. forces modernize the capital's infrastructure. By 1903, the new Republic of Cuba allows for the creation of a U.S. naval base in Guantanamo Bay in 1903, whose military moniker becomes "Gitmo."Cuban RevolutionIn 1959, Fidel Castro, his brother Raul and their band of bearded guerrillas stage a successful communist revolution overthrowing President Fulgencio Batista, a U.S. ally.Fidel Castro goes on to become one of the world's longest-ruling leaders, for more than 50 years, and one of the most vocal critics of capitalism and U.S. policies.U.S. embargoAfter the Cuban Revolution leads to the nationalization of about $1 billion of U.S.-owned property on the island, the U.S. government imposes a trade embargo on Cuba in 1960 that's designed to destabilize the communist regime. The Castros refer to this sanction as a "blockade" that they claim causes many of Cuba's problems.Bay of Pigs and missile crisisThe United States and Cuba come to the brink of nuclear war following a series of events that begins when U.S.-backed Cuban exiles invade the island at the Bay of Pigs. But the exiles suffer a crushing defeat in 1961, embarrassing the U.S. government.The following year, Cuba allows the Soviet Union to build missile installations on the isle, a major crisis in the Cold War. The standoff ends when the Soviet Union withdraws the missiles and the Americans promise not to invade Cuba. Secretly, Washington also agrees to remove U.S. ballistic missiles deployed in Turkey against the Soviets.Mariel exodusFlotillas of rafts and boats carry a mass movement of refugees from Cuba to Florida in 1980. In all, about 124,000 Cuban migrants take to the water and enter the United States. Fidel Castro enabled the exodus by allowing his people to leave Cuba freely from the port of Mariel.Elian GonzalezOnly 5, Elian Gonzalez is the only boat survivor of a group of refugees fleeing Cuba to Florida in 1999. An international incident erupts during a custody battle between the boy's father in Cuba and his relatives in the United States. At gunpoint, U.S. agents remove the boy from his great-uncle's home, and Elian is returned to Cuba in 2000.Gitmo Part IIAfter the September 11, 2001, attacks on the United States, President George W. Bush uses the Guantanamo Bay Naval Base as a detention facility for terror suspects. At its height, the facility hold more than 750 detainees and becomes a flashpoint of controversy about its legality as a prison and about alleged mistreatment of detainees.Under an agreement, the U.S. government sends Cuba about $4,085 a year to lease the land. Fidel Castro, however, is said to have called the U.S. base in Guantanamo "a dagger plunged into the Cuban soil," and the last time Cuba took the U.S. payments was in 1959, when the Castros took power.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023704-04-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023832-05-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031225-09-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023142-02-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031128-08-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023329-03-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031016-07-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015030059-06-cuban-missile-1015-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023704-04-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023832-05-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031225-09-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023142-02-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031128-08-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023329-03-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015031016-07-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015030059-06-cuban-missile-1015-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217090440-alan-gross-file-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217113524-alan-gross-arrival-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217093119-downtown-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217102439-obama-castro-split-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/111007033010-cuban-five-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121015023142-02-cuban-missile-1015-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141202102201-2016-republicans-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141218000425-perez-obama-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141128130939-cuba-flag-car-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130928163118-yasiel-puig-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141205115137-vatican-pope-audience-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/120711080942-little-havana-dominoes-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140611101328-alan-gross-us-cuba-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102191258im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141217092848-havana-cuba-video-tease.png</photos>
    </news>
</ns2:topic>
