<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns2:topic xmlns:ns2="http://schema/" topicid="1317376">
    <topicname>World</topicname>
    <news newsid="1319096">
        <title>Tiny hospital with big task: Identifying the victims of AirAsia Flight QZ8501</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/02/world/asia/hancocks-hospital-qz8501-remains/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>Red Cross and hospital workers in Pangkalan Bun, Indonesia receive bodies from downed airliner</highlights>
        <highlights>Hospital director says many of the victims are intact despite being found in the water</highlights>
        <highlights>Remains to be transported to Surabaya for formal identification by relatives</highlights>
        <highlights>AirAsia Flight QZ8501 failed to complete its journey from Surabaya to Singapore on Sunday</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T11:14:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Paula Hancocks, CNN</author>
        <content>Pangkalan Bun, Indonesia (CNN) -- A ten-minute warning sounds and everyone jumps into action. More bodies are on the way.Red Cross and hospital workers run to the front of the hospital in Pangkalan Bun, not even certain how many victims are coming.Sirens then announce the arrival of the remains of two innocent souls lost on AirAsia Flight QZ8501.Unfortunately, this little town in Indonesia's central Kalimantan Province has become the focal point for the recovery of bodies and debris from the airliner, which failed to complete its journey from Surabaya, the country's second-biggest city, to Singapore on Sunday.READ: Where things standOrange body bags are loaded onto gurneys and rushed to a separate, private wing of the hospital. The unmistakeable smell of death lingers long after the victims have passed.Their bodies are then cleaned and treated with chemicals to preserve them. It must be a gruesome and heartbreaking job.IdentificationThis is where the initial identification effort begins.Hospital staff assess gender, height, identifying marks and any clothing. But as time passes, the most obvious test -- facial recognition -- becomes increasingly difficult."Because they have been in the water some days, the bodies are bloated, but otherwise intact," says Suyuti Syamsul, director at the Sultan Imanuddin Hospital.He's been at the hospital 24 hours a day, he tells CNN, to ensure the bodies are afforded the respect they deserve.This hospital is not equipped for a tragedy on this scale.READ: Pilot's family tell of loving fatherThey usually have three morticians. They now have 40 staff and 20 volunteers focused on treating the bodies. The facility's other patients look on at the growing tragedy that has unfolded in this small town.Temporary caskets are being hastily made, some literally around the corner from where the bodies are being prepared.RespectSyamsul says they will have 162 coffins, one for each victim of the doomed flight. He says they are paying the victims every respect possible.Representatives of six different religions pray over the bodies before they leave. The victim's religion may not be known, but customs must still be observed."Their time on earth is over," says Pastor Sirdjon Palace. "So many of our prayers are for the family. We ask God to receive their bodies and give the families strength."A further six bodies arrived at Sultan Imanuddin hospital throughout Friday. Suyuti says 14 bodies have now come through the hospital so far.As the victims' remains are transported out by ambulance to be flown to Surabaya -- for formal identification by distraught families -- the hospital team takes a breath but just for a moment.The search, to the south of Pangkalan Bun, is slow going, hampered by rough seas, which complicate the job done by divers.With only ten victims recovered from the Java sea so far, there remain many more that will come through these gates, to be tended to by the small but dedicated group of workers here.On standby 24 hours a day, just waiting for the next ten-minute warning.READ: How can a modern airliner vanish?</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231122920-airasia-searcher-map-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101151334-nr-lkl-stevens-airasia-hamid-teacher-00012007-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231155729-pkg-tuchman-indonesia-family-loses-7-people-00001807-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101071713-01-airasia-0101-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231173852-airasia-grief-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231053007-airasia-search-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230132508-airasia-suitcase-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230194202-erin-dnt-stevens-airasia-bodies-and-debris-found-00004028-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071627-02-airasia-1229-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229111451-airasia-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231092416-airasia-search-pray-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182254-tsr-dnt-labott-airasia-crash-asian-airline-market-00000220-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229231219-ctn-intv-mh370-families-advice-to-airasia-familes-00000213-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228210218-nr-harlow-missing-airasia-update-00005323-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182806im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140721211119-mh17-black-box-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1320931">
        <title>The search for AirAsia Flight QZ8501: Where things stand</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/airasia-disaster/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: What may be a Flight 8501 window panel has been found, Singapore ministry says</highlights>
        <highlights>Thirty bodies have been recovered, officials say, and four of them have been identified</highlights>
        <highlights>Officials are focusing the search on a "most probable area" in the Java Sea</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T15:20:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Jethro Mullen, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Searchers looking for more bodies and wreckage from AirAsia Flight QZ8501 continue to be hindered by tough weather conditions.Ships, planes and helicopters are being used to try to find victims of the disaster. Most of the people on board the flight remain missing, and search teams are still looking for the main wreckage of the plane.Efforts are being concentrated in a zone covering 1,575 square nautical miles (5,400 square kilometers) that officials believe is the "most probable area" to find the remains of the aircraft.But on Friday, waves in the Java Sea as high as four meters (13 feet) were making it hard for divers search underwater.The weather is "the biggest obstacle," said Bambang Hermanu, chief of police in Indonesia's Central Kalimantan province, where much of the search operation is based.Here's more key information about where things stand on Flight QZ8501:The flightWhat we know: The aircraft took off early Sunday from Surabaya, Indonesia, bound for Singapore. Roughly 35 minutes into the flight, the pilot asked air traffic control for permission to turn left and climb to a higher altitude to avoid bad weather. Minutes later, the plane disappeared from air traffic control's radar.What we don't know: What happened on board after contact with the plane was lost. No distress call was received. Indonesian aviation authorities have suggested that the plane ascended despite permission being denied because of traffic.Some experts have speculated that the aircraft might have experienced an aerodynamic stall because of a lack of speed or from flying at too sharp an angle to get enough lift. Analysts have also suggested that the pilots might not have been getting information from onboard systems about the plane's position, or that rain or hail from thunderstorms in the area could have damaged the engines.Until the main wreckage of the plane is found, along with the flight recorders, experts have little evidence to support their theories.How can a modern airliner vanish?The searchWhat we know: Search teams found debris and some bodies in the water Tuesday, 100 to 200 kilometers (about 60 to 120 miles) from the aircraft's last known location over the Java Sea, Indonesia's search and rescue agency said. Thirty bodies have so far been recovered from the sea, Indonesian officials said Friday.Early Friday, what appears to be a piece of the fuselage was found, Singapore's Defense Ministry said. It resembles a window panel.The USS Sampson, the U.S. Navy ship that is helping with the search, recovered two bodies Thursday, the U.S. Seventh Fleet said Friday. Indonesia is leading the international search effort, with assistance from a range of countries including Malaysia, Singapore and the United States.What we don't know: The exact location of the body of the aircraft. An Indonesian search official told CNN on Wednesday that he thought sonar equipment had detected wreckage from Flight 8501 at the bottom of the Java Sea. But the country's search and rescue chief said the plane hadn't been found yet. Bad weather has hindered the search operation.The ones who missed the flightThe people on boardWhat we know: The plane was carrying 155 passengers and seven crew members. The overwhelming majority of those on board were Indonesians. There were also citizens of Britain, France, Malaysia, Singapore and South Korea. Details are emerging about some of the people on the flight, recounted by family members and friends.What we don't know: When the missing passengers and crew members will be recovered. Indonesian authorities have identified four of the recovered bodies so far. The first victim they identified, an Indonesian woman named Hayati Lutfiah Hamid, was buried Thursday. Many family members are waiting in Surabaya for news about their loved ones.Who was aboard AirAsia Flight QZ8501?The investigationWhat we know: The key to understanding what happened may be in the aircraft's cockpit voice recorder and flight data recorder, commonly known as black boxes. The black boxes, which are actually orange, are in the tail of Airbus 320-200s. If recovered, they will be taken to a lab in Jakarta, Indonesia, to be analyzed, said Tatang Kurniadi, head of Indonesia's National Committee for Transportation Safety. The batteries powering the "pingers" that send acoustic signals have only about 25 days of power left, he said.What we don't know: Where the plane's remains might have been taken by the elements. Investigators will need to use information gleaned from the flight recorders and clues from the wreckage."The more bits I can put into my mosaic, the better my picture will be," aviation safety expert Michael Barr said. "The better the picture, the better I can come up with an understanding of what happened." But the conditions at sea make that work much more difficult than on land. "In the water, you are working with currents and winds, and so the pieces won't be where they had the initial impact," he said.What happens next?The plane and the pilotsWhat we know: The 6-year-old Airbus A320-200, operated by AirAsia's Indonesian affiliate, had accumulated around 23,000 flight hours in about 13,600 flights, according to Airbus. The plane's last scheduled maintenance was on November 16.Flight 8501's veteran captain, Iriyanto, 53, had 20,537 flying hours, 6,100 of them with AirAsia on the Airbus A320, the airline said. The first officer, Remi Emmanuel Plesel, 46, had 2,275 flying hours, a reasonable amount for his position.What we don't know: Whether technical problems, human error or other issues were involved in the crash. According to information from the Aviation Safety Network accident database, there have been 54 incidents involving the A320."In the A320 family, accidents and incidents range from fan-cowl detachment, landing gear collapse, bird strikes, right through to hull losses through pilot error," said Kane Ray, an analyst with the International Bureau of Aviation, a global aviation consulting group. "Most aircraft have teething problems, and in most cases, these are eradicated. Very rarely, these issues cause disasters -- largely because of a culmination of factors that lead to the event," Ray said.Anguish revisited: Relatives of MH370 victims speakCNN's Elizabeth Joseph, Tim Schwarz, Paula Hancocks and David Molko contributed to this report. Journalist Yosef Riadi and translator Edi Pangerapan also contributed.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102050013-nr-molko-three-victims-id-including-airasia-flight-attendant-00003123-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102033509-nr-hancocks-six-more-bodies-airasia-crash-00000312-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101081647-newday-dnt-tuchman-airasia-recovery-mission-latest-00000403-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102083943-02-airasia-0102-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102070920-01-airasia-0102-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102072529-01-airasia-debris-0102-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101082734-01-airasia-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101082738-02-airasia-0101-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071347-01-airasia-1231-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071512-02-airasia-1231-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071613-03-airasia-1231-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071711-04-airasia-1231-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070140-04-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070326-05-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063116-01-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070425-06-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230163623-airasia-relative1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070524-07-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230102521-08-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063304-02-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063433-03-airasia-1230-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230164101-airasia-relative1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230165743-relatives-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229210848-01-airasia-tues-search-122914-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071308-01-airasia-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071713-03-airasia-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229101253-04-airasia-1229-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228174657-08-airasia-1228-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228094527-07-airasia-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228174840-09-airasia-1228-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228083732-06-airasia-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228074831-02-airasia-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228081535-04-airasia-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228074835-03-airasia-1228-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102083943-02-airasia-0102-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102070920-01-airasia-0102-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102072529-01-airasia-debris-0102-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101082734-01-airasia-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101082738-02-airasia-0101-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071347-01-airasia-1231-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071512-02-airasia-1231-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071613-03-airasia-1231-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231071711-04-airasia-1231-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070140-04-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070326-05-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063116-01-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070425-06-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230163623-airasia-relative1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230070524-07-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230102521-08-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063304-02-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230063433-03-airasia-1230-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230164101-airasia-relative1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230165743-relatives-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229210848-01-airasia-tues-search-122914-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071308-01-airasia-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071713-03-airasia-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229101253-04-airasia-1229-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228174657-08-airasia-1228-restricted-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228094527-07-airasia-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228174840-09-airasia-1228-restricted-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228083732-06-airasia-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228074831-02-airasia-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228081535-04-airasia-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228074835-03-airasia-1228-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102083943-02-airasia-0102-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102072529-01-airasia-debris-0102-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230115948-bts-ath-flores-victims-loved-ones-mourn-00002625-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230035950-families-of-airasia-8501-passengers-story-body.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230033204-airasia-map-debris-zone-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230033204-airasia-map-debris-zone-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101071713-01-airasia-0101-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231173852-airasia-grief-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231053007-airasia-search-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230132508-airasia-suitcase-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230194202-erin-dnt-stevens-airasia-bodies-and-debris-found-00004028-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071627-02-airasia-1229-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229111451-airasia-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231092416-airasia-search-pray-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182254-tsr-dnt-labott-airasia-crash-asian-airline-market-00000220-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229231219-ctn-intv-mh370-families-advice-to-airasia-familes-00000213-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228210218-nr-harlow-missing-airasia-update-00005323-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182807im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140721211119-mh17-black-box-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1322001">
        <title>Missed emails, hepatitis keep 15 from boarding doomed AirAsia Flight QZ8501</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/asia/airasia-missed-flight-fortunate-ones/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>It's an act of God that her father got hepatitis, says woman who canceled her family's flight</highlights>
        <highlights>Her brother forget to check emails, and it made their family miss the plane, another says</highlights>
        <highlights>Seven members of the two families who did not board QZ8501 are children</highlights>
        <highlights>Family members break down into tears when they hear the news of the missing plane</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T12:33:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Ben Brumfield, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- Some may call it serendipity, others divine intervention. Either way, circumstances prevented two families from boarding doomed AirAsia Flight QZ8501.In one case, it was missed emails. In another, an illness in the family. As a result, 15 people -- seven of them children -- are alive and well.'Truly a miracle'It was no stroke of luck but an act of God that her father caught hepatitis, said Inge Goreti Ferdiningsih, because it made her family cancel their tickets on the AirAsia flight a day before it took off."We are extremely grateful, and God is really great," she said. "I believe that God is saving and protecting us, and this is truly a miracle."Inge Goreti booked the family vacation nine months earlier. Her father wasn't booked on the trip, and her younger sister was staying by his side.So, Inge Goreti could still have gone, with her husband and three children.'Feeling in my heart'The bags stood packed and ready, and the family was full of anticipation for the Singapore vacation. Christopher 10, Nadine, 7, and Felix, 5, were psyched about taking a local ship cruise, splashing at a water park and watching animals perform at Sea World.But then Inge Goreti's sister called from a hospital, where she had taken their father after he complained of stomach pains. The diagnosis: hepatitis.The news tugged at her. "I had this feeling in my heart that I wanted to be with my dad," Inge Goreti said.So, she called off the trip Saturday, a day before the flight.Christopher had a hard time accepting it. He was so looking forward to the trip and became very upset, she said.'We were late'An aversion to phone messages may have spared another family.Christianawati was going to ring in the New Year in Singapore with her family and her brother's family, she told a French news agency. Ten were traveling in all.But her brother forgot to check messages from AirAsia telling them that the flight was leaving two hours before the original departure time."They emailed and called us on December 15 and 16 to inform us, but we missed those calls," Christianawati, who goes by one name, told Agence France-Presse."So we arrived at the airport to check in for the 7:30 a.m. flight but were told our flights had been rescheduled to 5:30 a.m., and we were late. Of course we were angry," she said.Some family members pulled up in their car just in time to see the last passengers whisk past them into the boarding lounge, The Sydney Morning Herald reported.But Christianawati's family was traveling in two cars, and one was lagging behind. They just missed the flight.Then they heard the news."Maybe it is all God's plan that my family and I were not on the flight," Christianawati said. "It was a blessing in disguise."Une famille échappe par miracle au vol d'@AirAsia http://t.co/rn6srTP6IB @AirAsiaBlog #Indonésie #Christianawati pic.twitter.com/j3DpjhlUJJ'Broke down and cried'Early Sunday, at Inge Goreti's home, the phone rang -- a few times."We received calls from relatives regarding the plane that lost contact," Inge Goreti said. "We all broke down and cried."Sunday evening, the family went to church to give thanks.But mixed with Inge Goreti's tears of relief have been tears of sadness. She recognized names on Flight QZ8501's passenger manifest, she said.Friends and colleagues were on board.CNN's Dorrine Mendoza and translator Azieza Uhnavy contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013010-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-family-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013010-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-family-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013702-ferdiningsih-flight-booking-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231013702-ferdiningsih-flight-booking-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101071713-01-airasia-0101-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231173852-airasia-grief-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231053007-airasia-search-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231021038-inge-goreti-ferdiningsih-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230132508-airasia-suitcase-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230194202-erin-dnt-stevens-airasia-bodies-and-debris-found-00004028-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229071627-02-airasia-1229-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229111451-airasia-map-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231092416-airasia-search-pray-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230182254-tsr-dnt-labott-airasia-crash-asian-airline-market-00000220-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228082113-05-airasia-1228-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141229231219-ctn-intv-mh370-families-advice-to-airasia-familes-00000213-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228210218-nr-harlow-missing-airasia-update-00005323-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140721211119-mh17-black-box-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1328763">
        <title>Icelandic coast guard ship tows stranded migrant vessel toward Italian coast</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/02/world/europe/italy-migrants-ship/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: About 60 children and many pregnant women are on the ship, coast guard says</highlights>
        <highlights>Ships are being "brought back from the dead" to carry migrants, official says</highlights>
        <highlights>An Icelandic coast guard vessel is towing the crewless, stranded Ezadeen to shore</highlights>
        <highlights>It's the second time this week that such a vessel has had to be rescued off Italy's coast</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T14:51:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Laura Smith-Spark, Barbie Latza Nadeau and Livia Borghese, CNN</author>
        <content>Rome (CNN) -- A crewless ship with hundreds of migrants aboard that was drifting without power off southeast Italy's coast is being towed to safety Friday by an Icelandic coast guard vessel.Italian authorities responded late Thursday to a distress call from the cargo ship Ezadeen, Italy's coast guard said. It's the second rescue of a crewless vessel off Italy's coast, in what appears to be a worrying new tactic by people traffickers.Overnight, the Ezadeen was at a standstill 58 miles (93 kilometers) off the coast of the city of Crotone in the Ionian Sea, the Italian coast guard said, where rescuers were trying to restart the boat's engines.The Icelandic coast guard said its vessel Tyr was now working as part of an Italian-led operation to tow the stranded ship to shore.Italy's coast guard said the Tyr was expected to reach the port of Corigliano Calabro at midnight local time (6 p.m ET). It was unable to dock at a nearer port because of the ship's limited maneuverability, the coast guard said.The Tyr was doing surveillance for Frontex, the European Union border management agency, when it was called in to help.Six Italian and four Icelandic coast guard crew members are now aboard the vessel, the Italian coast guard said. As well as taking control of the ship, they brought food and water for its passengers, who include 50 to 60 children and many pregnant women, the coast guard said. No medical emergency has been reported.An initial survey indicated between 400 and 450 people on the ship, the coast guard said, adding that the exact number has not been checked since the priority is to bring the ship into a safe port.UN: 3,000 died in 2014 trying to get to EuropeThe Italian air force and coast guard said Thursday that weather conditions had made the rescue operation very challenging, with coast guard crew members having to be taken by helicopter to the ship, which is flying the flag of Sierra Leone.The alarm was raised when migrants launched an SOS, said Floriana Segreto, a spokeswoman for the Italian coast guard.Since last September, she told CNN, there have been 15 similar cargo ships carrying mainly migrants from Syria who are wealthier and can pay more than others who are forced to travel on smaller, rickety boats.She cited the International Organization for Migration as saying the price for each passenger was about 6,000 euros ($7,260), with a reduction if there are more than 250 passengers on board.Such cargo ships leave from a Greek or Turkish port with the migrants already on board, she said. They are old merchant ships that "should not be navigating in the Mediterranean Sea," she said, and still have a flag, as in the case of the Ezadeen, or carry a fake flag.They sail in Turkish or Greek waters without rousing suspicion and appear to be normal merchant ships, Segreto said.However, once in Italian "save and rescue" operational waters, they launch a mayday via satellite phone to a humanitarian association or directly to the Italian coast guard, she said.The smugglers then either abandon ship or mix in with the migrants. Only when all passengers are questioned on shore do investigators have a chance to identify the smugglers, Segreto said.'Multimillion-dollar business'Frontex spokeswoman Ewa Moncure drew a parallel between what happened on the Ezadeen and on the Blue Sky M, a freighter that was also apparently abandoned this week by its crew with almost 800 people aboard, most believed to be migrants from war-torn Syria. It docked safely in the southern port of Gallipoli on Wednesday after the Italian coast guard seized control.In each case, human traffickers appear to have employed the same method of using large, decommissioned cargo ships that have been "brought back from the dead," Moncure said.It's a "multimillion-dollar business" for those operating such ships, she said. Moncure estimates that each passenger paid $3,000 to travel on the Ezadeen.While their work is focused on border control, Frontex vessels -- provided by EU member states -- are obliged to help in search-and-rescue situations, Moncure said.With ever-increasing numbers of migrants from such countries as Syria and Eritrea putting their lives in the hands of unscrupulous traffickers, their efforts are sorely needed.Faced with a crisis off its shores, Italy launched Operation Mare Nostrum ("Our Sea") to try to find and rescue stranded migrants. It has now scaled back the project, which cost Italians 9 million euros ($10.9 million) a month from November 2013 to the end of 2014.In October, the European Union announced that Frontex would launch its own operation, dubbed Triton, in the central Mediterranean to help fill the gap.EU Commissioner Cecilia Malmstrom, said the new Frontex operation would "show concrete solidarity to Italy, by reinforcing its border surveillance and supporting its humanitarian efforts."But, she said, "It is clear that the Triton operation cannot and will not replace Mare Nostrum."Ships equipped with cells, quarantine areasWhile Operation Mare Nostrum is over in name, Italian naval assets are still carrying out rescues in cooperation with Frontex vessels, which call them in to help.The San Giorgio, a navy ship that was converted to rescue migrants under Mare Nostrum and which was the primary rescue vehicle, is still active in such missions and was used last week to rescue those on board the burning Greek ferry, Norman Atlantic.It is equipped with an infirmary, jail cells for smugglers, quarantine sections for potential Ebola patients, and sleeping quarters for the migrants.CNN went out last month on a Frontex patrol on the San Mino, a Japanese fishing vessel converted into a Spanish coast guard ship.Jose Maria Duenas, commander of the San Mino, said that the crew do see themselves as search and rescue. "We are not turning migrants back, we are rescuing them," he said.Report: 40,000 migrant deaths since 2000Dangerous sea routesAmid continued migrant deaths at sea, rights group Amnesty International warned last month that Triton was "vastly reduced in scale and area covered" compared with Mare Nostrum and called on EU nations to step up their efforts."People are still taking these dangerous sea routes to get to Europe. If the EU is serious about preventing the Mediterranean from becoming a cemetery, it must be prepared to deploy search-and-rescue operations all along the routes that desperate refugees and migrants are taking," said John Dalhuisen, Amnesty International's director for Europe and Central Asia.A spokeswoman for the EU Commission said Friday that it was closely following the Ezadeen situation."The rescues of the Blue Sky M two days ago and of the Ezadeen show that smugglers are finding new ways to enter EU territory," she said."To prevent such events and to protect the lives of migrants, fighting smuggling will continue to be a priority under the Commission's agenda for comprehensive migration in 2015."More than 207,000 people crossed the Mediterranean for Europe illegally in 2014, the High Commissioner for Refugees, the U.N. refugee agency, said last month -- almost three times the previous high of about 70,000 in 2011. That's 60% of roughly 348,000 boat migrants worldwide last year."Europe, facing conflicts to its south (Libya), east (Ukraine) and south-east (Syria/Iraq) is seeing the largest number of sea arrivals," the UNHCR said.More than 3,400 of those seeking to reach Europe last year died, many of them drowning after being trafficked in unseaworthy vessels from the shores of the Middle East and North Africa across the Mediterranean.Journalists Barbie Latza Nadeau and Livia Borghese reported from Rome and Laura Smith-Spark wrote and reported from London. CNN's Sweelin Ong and Sara Delgrossi contributed to this report.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231110216-crewless-ship-story-body.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141231101011-airasia-searchers-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228191135-air-asia-missing-plane-pk-axc-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140206110311-african-students-association-somalia-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141209115854-beijing-smog-split-screen-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140812174415-michael-muller-shark-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224130840-spc-tomorrow-transformed-power-people-00013819-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140311131158-tim-berners-lee-lyonj-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141210104907-out-of-the-phone-bengchia-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222155638-elbagir-boko-haram-video-released-00003125-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203043607-21a-poy-2014-1203-restricted-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910170757-defining-moments-supermoon-seville-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140114192625-wesley-chapel-sunset-scenes-from-the-field-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1329767">
        <title>3 soldiers killed in Kashmir gunfight between India and Pakistan</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/kashmir-violence/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>Pakistani military says Indian side shot first</highlights>
        <highlights>Indian military: Pakistani rangers shot and killed an Indian soldier on New Year's Eve</highlights>
        <highlights>Bilateral ceasefire agreement held for years, but there have been recent breaches</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T21:22:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Mukhtar Ahmad and Adeel Raja, CNN</author>
        <content>Kashmir (CNN) -- The sound of gunfire marked New Year's Eve in the tense disputed region of Kashmir between India and Pakistan.Pakistani rangers shot and killed an Indian soldier, India's military said. India's military shot and killed two Pakistani rangers, Pakistan's military said.Both sides claimed that the other started the gunfight.Indian military spokesman Dharminder Parikh said Pakistani rangers opened fire unprovoked at Indian positions in the Samba sector of Indian-administered Kashmir as the old year was coming to a close. A second Indian border soldier was wounded in the fight, he said.Pakistan's Punjab Rangers said that their Indian counterparts had a meeting, and when two rangers contacted them, the Indian side opened fire. The two were wounded and later died, they said.The two nuclear-armed South Asian neighbors had agreed to a bilateral ceasefire in border regions in November 2003, and the agreement held for years.But there have been breaches in recent years.Kashmir has been in the throes of separatist violence since 1989, which has claimed over 43,000 lives.Indian soldiers killed in gunfight with militants in Kashmir</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1331342">
        <title>Man kills 8 people in Edmonton before committing suicide, police say</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/americas/edmonton-killings/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Alberta premier extends condolences to people affected by the slayings</highlights>
        <highlights>Family feared suspected killer was suicidal, police say</highlights>
        <highlights>9 bodies found at three crime scenes in western Canada</highlights>
        <highlights>Police chief says it was a domestic dispute</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-31T12:13:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Ralph Ellis, CNN</author>
        <content>(CNN) -- A man described by his family as "depressed and overly emotional" is suspected of killing eight people before taking his own life, police in Edmonton, Alberta, said Tuesday.Seven of the victims, including two children, were found inside a house in north Edmonton, said Edmonton Police Chief Ron Knecht."This series of events are not believed to be random acts and there is no risk to the broader public," he said. "These events do not appear to be gang related but rather tragic incidents of domestic violence."This is the worst mass violence in Edmonton, a city of about 812,000 people in the western Canada province of Alberta, since six people were killed in 1956, Knecht said.So far, authorities have identified one victim, 37-year-old Cyndi Duong. Knech said all the victims are connected.Knecht said officers first went to a residence in southwest Edmonton about 7 p.m. Monday after receiving a weapons complaint."It is alleged a male entered a private residence, discharged a firearm and fled," he said.Inside the house, officers found a dead middle-aged woman.About 8:30 p.m. Monday, police received a call asking them to check on a man at a house in north Edmonton, Knecht said."According to the family, the male seemed depressed and overly emotional," Knecht said. "The family was concerned the male might be suicidal."Police didn't receive a response when they went to the house and noticed nothing suspicious, the chief said.Around 12:30 a.m. Tuesday, police received more information and returned to the house in north Edmonton. Inside, they found seven people dead: three adult women, two adult males, a male child and a female child, Knecht said.Knecht said police were told at 2:20 a.m. Tuesday that a black SUV connected to the first killing had been seen near a restaurant in Fort Saskatchewan, about 20 miles from Edmonton.Police surrounded the business and determined at 8:45 a.m. that a man inside the restaurant was dead from an apparent self-inflicted gunshot wound, Knecht said.Police said he is the man whose family had been worried about his welfare the night before."We are not looking for other suspects," Knecht said.Alberta Premier Jim Prentice said, "We trust that the police agencies' investigations will help provide answers as we struggle to understand this tragic turn of events. In the meantime, on behalf of the government of Alberta, I extend our deepest condolences to the people affected by this incident, and our appreciation to public servants who provided a professional response during what must have been dangerous and difficult circumstances."Suspect in Pennsylvania family massacre kills 6</content>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1333008">
        <title>Jordanian pilot shown in ISIS' propaganda magazine</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/world/meast/syria-isis-jordanian-magazine/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>ISIS has published what it claims is an "interview" with a Jordanian pilot captured in Syria</highlights>
        <highlights>ISIS says it downed an F-16 manned by Moaz al-Kassasbeh during coalition air strikes</highlights>
        <highlights>A still image of al-Kassasbeh wearing an orange jumpsuit tops the short article</highlights>
        <highlights>The magazine also contains an article claimed to have been authored by Briton John Cantlie</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T20:33:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Salma Abdelaziz, CNN</author>
        <content>Abu Dhabi (CNN) -- "Do you know what the Islamic State (ISIS) will do with you?" members of the terrorist group's propaganda wing ask their captive, who appears to be wearing an orange jumpsuit. "Yes. They will kill me," the hostage replies.The Islamic State in Iraq and Syria has just published in its latest English-language magazine Dabiq what it claims is an "interview" with the Jordanian pilot captured in Syria.Militants say they downed an F-16 jet manned by Moaz al-Kassasbeh as he took part in U.S.-led coalition air strikes near ISIS's de-facto capital, Raqqah, last week. Images provided by the extremist organization's media wing and circulated widely on social media showed bearded men with Kalashnikovs pulling the terrified airman out of a nearby river."We entered the region of Raqqah to sweep the area, then the striker jets entered to begin their attack," al-Kassasbeh said, according to the online publication. "My plane was struck by a heat-seeking missile. I heard and felt its hit."The Jordanian government and U.S. Central Command described the incident as an aircraft crash and adamantly stated that it was not shot down by ISIS."I checked the system display and it indicated that the engine was damaged and burning," the pilot is quoted as saying. "The plane began to deviate from its normal flight path, so I ejected. I landed in the Furat River by parachute and the seat caught on some ground, keeping me fixed, until I was captured by soldiers of the Islamic State."A still image of al-Kassasbeh wearing the orange jumpsuit tops the short article titled: "The Capture of the Crusader Pilot." Journalist James Foley, American NGO founder Peter Kassig, and British aid worker Alan Henning among other hostages wore similar outfits in videos purporting to show their murders at the hands of the extremists.The magazine also contains an article claimed to have been authored by British hostage John Cantlie, headlined "Meltdown." The article suggests the world is facing economic collapse and says "it makes enormous sense for the Islamic State to mint their own gold dinars." Cantlie was a photojournalist and freelance writer for major British newspapers, before he was kidnapped in November 2012 along with American journalist James Foley, who was also killed by ISIS militants.The family of the captured Jordanian pilot have made several emotional pleas for his release and called on the Jordanian government to launch an investigation into the crash."Be supportive of our brother Moaz and to be merciful on him, please send him back to us," Jawad al-Kassasbeh told CNN Arabic last Friday. "He is just a soldier who is following orders and has no authority."Jordan, is one of several nations participating in an American-led mission against ISIS, an organization which is seeking to establish a Caliphate, or Islamic State, and has wrested territory spanning from central Syria to about 100km (62 miles) north of Baghdad.The United Nations says the group's acts of brutality, including the enslavement of women, mass killing, and the torture and imprisonment of its enemies, amount to war crimes and crimes against humanity.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226114904-moaz-al-kassasbeh-jordanian-pilot-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226155411-cnni-vo-father-plea-captured-son-isis-00010618-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226114904-moaz-al-kassasbeh-jordanian-pilot-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141225185243-vo-isis-mosul-governor-00001109-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222000437-pkg-pleitgen-german-journalist-inside-isis-00014927-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141117103601-isis-masked-militant-flag-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141201174552-lead-dnt-sciutto-us-troops-warned-of-isis-attacks-00013503-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141201101458-pkg-karadsheh-iraq-ghost-soldiers-00004403-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141201181359-tsr-starr-secretary-of-defense-isis-00003315-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141112182823-tsr-intv-royce-blitzer-new-isis-strategy-00002405-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141112111722-pkg-damon-teenager-isis-00001025-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141112172840-jihadi-janes-brown-pkg-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141104205927-intv-reza-aslan-the-appeal-of-isis-00032202-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141102201540-dnt-walsh-children-brainwashed-by-isis-00005117-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141026183531-pkg-kaye-isis-recruiting-canadians-00003722-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102182827im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140925105348-isis-fighter-al-hayat-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1334490">
        <title>Hundreds of migrants rescued as Italy's coast guard averts ship crash</title>
        <url>/web/20150102171512/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/31/world/europe/italy-migrant-vessel/index.html?hpt=wo_c2</url>
        <highlights>NEW: Italy's coast guard says there were 796 migrants aboard the ship</highlights>
        <highlights>The crew had abandoned the freighter, which was cruising toward the rocky coast</highlights>
        <highlights>Italian coast guard brought the freighter packed with migrants safely into port</highlights>
        <highlights>The coast guard says its action saved lives, prevented an environmental disaster</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T10:40:00.000Z</date>
        <author>By Livia Borghese, CNN</author>
        <content>Rome (CNN) -- It could have been, in the words of the Italian coast guard, a disaster.But thanks to authorities, a ship on course to crash against the rocky Italian coast was stopped in time, saving passengers and averting a possible environmental catastrophe.Italian coast guard commander Filippo Marini said the vessel was cruising on autopilot toward the coast at 6 nautical miles per hour. When it entered Italian search and rescue waters, the coast guard sent helicopters with six men, who boarded the ship and took control.The course of the vessel was reversed to avoid a collision with the rocks, and it was piloted instead to Gallipoli, in Italy's southern Puglia region. It docked safely there Wednesday.The freighter carried 796 migrants, the coast guard said Thursday, most believed to be from war-torn Syria. Authorities on Wednesday put the number of migrants on board at 768.The crew of the Blue Sky M apparently jumped ship.The coast guard said a collision would not only have led to the deaths of passengers, but would also have created an environmental disaster. It said a "real disaster" was avoided.The freighter sent a distress signal near the Greek island of Corfu on Tuesday, alerting Italian and Greek authorities to the situation on board.The Greek Merchant Marine Ministry and the Greek Navy have said the pilot of a Greek helicopter that flew over the cargo ship spoke with the captain, who said the ship was not in distress and did not need assistance.Floriana Segreto, a spokeswoman for the Italian coast guard in Rome, said there were no deaths related to the Blue Sky M incident. She added that about 100 people have been hospitalized, mainly because of the cold and exhaustion.It was not immediately clear where the migrants will go.The authorities will investigate what happened to the crew and how the freighter reached Italy's waters.</content>
    </news>
</ns2:topic>
