<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns2:topic xmlns:ns2="http://schema/" topicid="1429543">
    <topicname>World Sport</topicname>
    <news newsid="1430462">
        <title>Rafael Nadal not worried after being crushed in latest tennis comeback</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/02/sport/tennis/nadal-comeback-tennis-murray/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Andy Murray routs Rafael Nadal 6-2 6-0 at the Mubadala exhibition tournament</highlights>
        <highlights>The semifinal in Abu Dhabi marked Nadal's comeback from appendix surgery</highlights>
        <highlights>The 14-time grand slam winner also suffered back and wrist injuries in 2014</highlights>
        <highlights>Murray meets Novak Djokovic in Saturday's final after the Serb beat Stan Wawrinka</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-02T17:37:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- With all the health setbacks he has endured, Rafael Nadal is used to comebacks.He made another one Friday at the exhibition Mubadala World Tennis Championship in Abu Dhabi but it didn't last long, as the 14-time grand slam champion was crushed by Andy Murray 6-2 6-0 in the semifinals.While Nadal most certainly would have wanted to put up a better showing, he'll probably just be happy -- for the moment -- that he has physically recovered from the appendix surgery that forced him to skip the year-end ATP World Tour Finals in London last November.He'll have a little over two weeks to find his game before the start of the year's first grand slam, the Australian Open, and he vows to make progress.Next week the Spaniard -- who suffered a back injury in last year's Australian Open final and skipped last year's U.S. Open with a wrist complaint -- competes at the Qatar Open in nearby Doha."There are only small things I need to adjust," Nadal, who has competed in just three ATP tournaments since Wimbledon, was quoted as saying by the Gulf News."6-2 6-0 is too much -- I had a lot of chances to have a closer result," he added. "I have to improve, that's obvious, and I'm going to improve. This match helps me and the defeat does not affect me too much."I felt I was dominating the points a lot of times, but I am missing competitive spirit. I am going to keep working hard."Murray, too, knows what it's like to return from injuries.The two-time grand slam winner from Scotland underwent back surgery late in 2013 and never really found his form in 2014, achieving one grand slam semifinal.His body is feeling better, though.The off-season has certainly been eventful for Murray. He cut ties with his co-coach and good friend Dani Vallverdu and longtime fitness trainer Jez Green. In happier news, however, he announced his engagement to girlfriend Kim Sears.Murray faces a rematch with world No. 1 Novak Djokovic -- Murray's pal and victim in both of his successes in grand slam finals -- on Saturday.Djokovic ousted Switzerland's Stan Wawrinka 6-1 6-2 in the other semifinal. It was Wawrinka who upended the Serb en route to the Australian Open title in 2014, breaking up the dominance of the Big Four.Read: Can Nadal's mind conquer ailing body?</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150102101746-nadal-top-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141222104152-spc-open-court-rafa-nadal-manacor-academy-00001706-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140602150134-pkg-french-open-racquets-nadal-00023321-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130911025849-intv-rafa-nadal-us-open-win-00023207-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216113717-nadal-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141123082755-federer-win-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141127132728-andy-murray-and-kim-sears-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140317135210-rene-lacoste-reptile-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908173716-cilic-top3-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908142559-serena-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140829175927-gibson-wimbledon-trophy-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140827124247-eugenie-bouchard-canada-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140820173159-boris-becker-wimbledon-final-2014-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140819180006-boris-becker-head-shot-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722140154-emmrich-and-krajicek-hug-video-tease.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140306105751-aga-lisicki-top-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140617174025-maria-sharapova-wimbledon-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140414163611-yannick-noah-gal-8-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150103035955im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140429120509-hingis-tennis-smile-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1431392">
        <title>Harry Kane stuns Chelsea as Man City draws level at top of EPL</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2015/01/01/sport/football/football-epl-chelsea-man-utd/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Tottenham beats Chelsea 5-3 at White Hart Lane</highlights>
        <highlights>Man City level at top after 3-2 victory over Sunderland with Frank Lampard scoring winner</highlights>
        <highlights>Man Utd held to 1-1 draw at Stoke in early kick off</highlights>
        <highlights>WBA confirms Tony Pulis as new head coach</highlights>
        <date>2015-01-01T21:21:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Chelsea relinquished sole leadership of the English Premier League after suffering a surprise 5-3 defeat at the hands of a Harry Kane inspired Tottenham Hotspur at White Hart Lane Thursday.It was a result few had foreseen, particularly when Diego Costa put Jose Mourinho's men ahead midway through the first half.But Kane, pushing for an England call up, leveled with an exquisite individual goal and Danny Rose put Spurs 2-1 ahead after he reacted quickly when Nacer Chadli's shot hit the post and rebounded back into play.Kane was then fouled by Gary Cahill with Andros Townsend scoring from the penalty spot to give the home side a 3-1 lead at the break.It was 4-1 shortly into the second half when Kane's neat footwork set him up for a fourth, but still the points were not sealed.A mistake by Federico Fazio allowed Eden Hazard to play a one-two with Cesc Fabregas to reduce the deficit to two goals.Read: Chelsea stays top after Boxing Day winTottenham nerves were finally eased when Kane played a neat pass to Chadli for the Belgian international to score the fifth only for John Terry to grab his third in four games for Chelsea to complete an eight-goal thriller.Earlier, Manchester City joined Chelsea on 46 points with the same goal difference after a headed goal from former Chelsea star Frank Lampard gave the reigning title holder a 3-2 win over Sunderland.Lampard, whose extended loan to City from New York City was confirmed on the eve of the match, grabbed a late winner after City had thrown away a two-goal lead at the Etihad.The 36-year-old former England midfielder connected with Gael Clichy's cross to secure a vital three points with a seventh home league win of the season.City looked to be cruising to victory after a superb strike from Yaya Toure and a second from Stevan Jovetic.But Sunderland hit back with goals from former City players Jack Rodwell and Adam Johnson, who scored from the spot.In the early kickoff on New Year's Day, Manchester United was held to its second straight draw of the festive period in a 1-1 draw at Stoke.Read: Man City blows chance to join Chelsea at topThe home side went ahead after just two minutes through defender Ryan Shawcross but Radamel Falcao leveled for United in the 26th.United, held goalless at Tottenham last weekend, remain third in the standings and are unbeaten in 10 games, but manager Louis Van Gaal was unhappy with the display."We didn't deserve any more than a draw," he moaned. "They were closer to a winning goal than us. We should have played better today."Struggling West Bromwich Albion has also confirmed the appointment of former Stoke and Crystal Palace boss Tony Pulis as its head coach.Pulis, widely praised for lifting Palace into mid-table last season before leaving before the start of this campaign, watched from the stand as his new team secured a fighting 1-1 draw at West Ham.Southampton kept up its challenge for a Champions League spot by inflicting a damaging 2-0 defeat on Arsenal to stay fourth.Two goalkeeping errors from Wojciech Szczesny allowed Sadio Mane and Dusan Tadic to score in either half for the Saints, who withstood late pressure from Arsenal to secure a vital three points.In the relegation battle, bottom side Leicester secured an unlikely point after hitting back from two down at Liverpool to grab a 2-2 draw, while Burnley hit back three times to level 3-3 at Newcastle.It denied Newcastle caretaker boss John Carver three points after taking over from Alan Pardew, who is set to link up with Crystal Palace and was at Villa Park to watch them battle to a goalless draw.Read: Ronaldo immortalized in bronze</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/150101192757-harry-kane-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216100552-henry-new-york-laughing-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605114319-eibar-gal-9-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017152545-gallery-real-madrid-refurb-6-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141027022422-bpr-south-african-soccor-senzo-meyiwa-death-00000402-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020180630-roma-centurion-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020132745-kreshnik-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017150734-ched-evans-smiling-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016105457-lionel-messi-opener-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122943-inter-milan-fan-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013170740-martin-odegaard-norway-debut-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010121745-indian-football-league-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002124314-davies-intv-rio-ferdinand-racism-00002712-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192808im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908152849-odegaard-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1432718">
        <title>Barcelona ready to hit back after transfer ban appeal fails</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/sport/barcelona-hit-with-transfer-ban/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Barcelona's appeal against transfer ban dismissed by Court of Arbitration of Sport</highlights>
        <highlights>Club found guilty of breaching FIFA rules on the transfer of players under 18</highlights>
        <highlights>Barcelona says it could make fresh appeal</highlights>
        <highlights>Club was initially hit with ban in April which was suspended pending two appeals</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-30T14:45:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Barcelona says the transfer ban placed on the club is "disproportionate" and "excessive."The Catalan club hit back on Tuesday after losing its appeal to the Court of Arbitration of Sport (CAS) following the decision to ban it from being able to sign new players over the next 12 months.CAS stated that Barcelona was guilty of breaching FIFA rules on signing minors and confirmed that the club would be unable to add to its squad during the next two transfer windows."The Panel found in particular that FC Barcelona had breached the rules regarding the protection of minors and the registration of minors attending football academies. Accordingly, the FIFA decision is confirmed in full and the sanction remains in force," a CAS statement read.FC Barcelona statement regarding CAS verdict http://t.co/vTzfdsbl5p pic.twitter.com/hScbDyzFaDBarcelona, which was also fined $455,000, said it "totally disagrees" with the verdict and will now study the different legal options at its disposal including the Swiss Federal Courts.Read: Barcelona hit with transfer ban by FIFAIn a statement, Barcelona said that it "understands and supports the policy on the protection of minors and the concern for the protection of their development and education."It added: "This is confirmed by how the club has acted throughout its history, setting an example around the world for the way its young footballers are schooled and educated, and the work that is done on their development. FC Barcelona's youth structure has enabled hundreds of young players to achieve their dreams and receive a decent upbringing."The errors that the club might have committed, and which have been recognized and argued before the corresponding authorities are, in all cases, of an administrative nature and to a large extent have been caused by the existing conflict between the FIFA regulations and Spanish legislation, along with the club's conviction that it was acting correctly."Therefore, FC Barcelona considers the sanction to be completely disproportionate as it supposes an excessive punishment for the club, when considering its trajectory and the circumstances of this specific case."Barcelona has one of the most famous and successful academies in the game with young players from all over the world learning their trade with the club."La Masia" as it is known, has helped produced talents such as Lionel Messi, who arrived from Argentina at the age of 11.The ruling comes after an investigation found the club had broken regulations regarding the transfer of young players from outside Spain.FIFA's investigation focused on several players aged under 18 who were registered and played for the club between 2009 and 2013.Under FIFA laws, clubs are not allowed to sign international players under the age of 18 unless the player is moving within the European Union, is aged between 16 and 18 and moving with their parents or the club and the player both live within 50 kilometers of a shared national border.Barcelona was originally handed a 14-month ban in April but launched an appeal to FIFA, world football's governing body which was rejected in August.But the decision to appeal to CAS meant Barcelona was allowed to complete a number of signings in the intervening period.Barcelona splashed out a reported $128.5 million to sign Uruguay international Luis Suarez from Liverpool.Belgian defender Thomas Vermaelen was brought in from Arsenal for $30m while French defender Jeremy Mathieu and Chilean goalkeeper Claudio Bravo also arrived at Camp Nou.Croatian midfielder Ivan Rakitic from Sevilla joined Barca for a fee of $23.9m with the club also paying $3m to Dinamo Zagreb for Alen Halilovic.Luis Enrique's side currently sits second in La Liga, one point behind fierce rival Real Madrid.Read: Barcelona's appeal against transfer ban rejected</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141125211304-messi-ucl-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140711132710-suarez-barcelona-image-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140403175535-exp-barca-fifa-legal-opinion-00002221-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140123160223-rosell-presser-jan-23-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216100552-henry-new-york-laughing-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605114319-eibar-gal-9-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017152545-gallery-real-madrid-refurb-6-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141027022422-bpr-south-african-soccor-senzo-meyiwa-death-00000402-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020180630-roma-centurion-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020132745-kreshnik-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017150734-ched-evans-smiling-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016105457-lionel-messi-opener-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122943-inter-milan-fan-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013170740-martin-odegaard-norway-debut-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010121745-indian-football-league-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002124314-davies-intv-rio-ferdinand-racism-00002712-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192809im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908152849-odegaard-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1433945">
        <title>Mahendra Singh Dhoni retires from Test match cricket</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/30/sport/cricket-mahendra-singh-dhoni-retires/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>MS Dhoni has retired from Test cricket</highlights>
        <highlights>Indian captain made announcement after series defeat by Australia</highlights>
        <highlights>Dhoni led India to 27 victories in 60 Test matches as captain</highlights>
        <highlights>The 33-year-old will now concentrate on one-day and Twenty20 cricket</highlights>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- He is India's most successful Test match captain but Mahendra Singh Dhoni has decided enough is enough.The 33-year-old has retired from Test match cricket, bringing down the curtain on an illustrious career in which he thrilled crowds across the world.Dhoni, who made his debut in 2005, captained India in 60 of his 90 Test matches but decided to quit on Tuesday following the draw with Australia in Melbourne which meant his side conceded the series.In a statement, the Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI), said that Dhoni made the decision to retire from Tests "in order to concentrate" on one-day and Twenty20 cricket."One of India's greatest Test Captains under whose leadership India became the No. 1 team in the Test Rankings MS Dhoni, has decided to retire from Test Cricket citing the strain of playing all formats of Cricket," said the statement."MS Dhoni has chosen to retire from Test Cricket with immediate effect in order to concentrate on ODI and T20 formats."BCCI while respecting the decision of MS Dhoni to retire from Test Cricket, wishes to thank him for his enormous contribution to Test Cricket and the laurels that he has brought to India."The decision comes following a difficult year for Dhoni, who has been hampered by a succession of injuries.The wicket-keeper batsman missed five one-day games against Sri Lanka in November after suffering a hand injury, the same problem which forced him out of the opening Test against Australia earlier this month.That should not detract from a stellar career in which Dhoni has become India's highest earning sports star.According to Forbes, he is the fourth highest earning sportsman in the world, raking in $20 million in 2014, placing him ahead of Cristiano Ronaldo, Usain Bolt, Kobe Bryant and Lionel Messi.well done on a wonderful career in test cricket @msdhoni. Always enjoyed playing together. Next target 2015 WC my friend!!His decision comes just weeks ahead of the World Cup in Australia and New Zealand where India will defend its one-day crown.Dhoni will now start preparing for the tournament while Virat Kohli, one of the team's star batsmen, takes charge of the final Test match against Australia in Sydney which starts on January 6.Trailing 2-0 in the four match series, India required victory in Melbourne to keep the series alive.The draw meant that it was unable to overturn the deficit and slumped to yet another overseas defeat -- a recurring theme during Dhoni's reign.Since 2011, India has managed to win just two out of 22 away Tests and lost 13.During his 90-match Test career, Dhoni scored 4,876 runs at an average of 38.09, while his highest score of 224 came against Australia in February 2013.The wicket-keeper batsman also claimed 256 catches and made 38 stumpings.Dhoni replaced Anil Kumble as captain in 2008 after guiding India to victory in the very first World Twenty20 title the previous year.He enjoyed a hugely successful start to his reign, losing just one of 13 Test series and winning eight.Valiant while you led. Valiant in your departure. #Respect @msdhoni pic.twitter.com/w6xdnebG3sThat run allowed India to top the world rankings towards the end of 2009, a position in which it remained until 2011.But India has struggled for success outside of its own country in the Test match arena in recent times.This latest defeat by Australia comes on the back of similar results in England, New Zealand and South Africa.Last August, Dhoni hinted he may leave his role as captain after his side's 3-1 Test series defeat by England.When asked if he had taken his team as far as possible, he said: "Maybe, yes."You'll have to wait and watch. If I'm strong enough or not strong enough, you'll have to wait and get the news."India begins its defense of the World Cup title on February 15 against Pakistan in Adelaide.It will also face South Africa, West Indies, Zimbabwe, Ireland and United Arab Emirates in the group stages.Dhoni has excelled in the one-day game having made 250 appearances for India.He has scored 8,192 runs at an average of 52.85.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230153741-dhoni-batting-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151635-dhoni-gloves-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151543-dhoni-retire-handshake-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151447-dhoni-captain-debut-vertical-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151334-dhoni-diving-catch-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151245-dhoni-first-100-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151124-dhoni-debut-behind-stumps-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230153741-dhoni-batting-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151635-dhoni-gloves-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151543-dhoni-retire-handshake-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151447-dhoni-captain-debut-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151334-dhoni-diving-catch-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151245-dhoni-first-100-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141230151124-dhoni-debut-behind-stumps-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131117235645-intv-kapur-india-cricket-sachin-tendulkar-retires-long-00033807-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131118000825-pkg-kapur-india-sachin-tendulkar-farewell-00002627-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131117121429-intv-sachin-tendulkar-cricket-00004609-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140417073226-pkg-daftari-ipl-in-uae-00012514-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131228140059-australia-piers-morgan-hit-by-cricket-ball-00004230-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131117235645-intv-kapur-india-cricket-sachin-tendulkar-retires-long-00033807-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140106135611-gary-kirsten-lawrence-rowe-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131229174609-jacques-kallis-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/121223024705-sachin-tendulkar-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130304105434-franklyn-stephenson-west-indies-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130306142217-franklyn-stephenson-1983-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130301145748-basil-cricket-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130304104407-collis-king-wsp-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130307122248-branded-rebel-cricket-ron-b-00003115-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192810im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130403120144-h2h-afghan-cricket-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1435187">
        <title>Man City blows chance to close gap on Chelsea in Premier League</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/28/sport/football/man-city-chelsea-football-premier-league/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Manchester City blows two-goal lead at home and draws lowly Burnley 2-2</highlights>
        <highlights>Chelsea had earlier drawn 10-man Southampton 1-1 away from home</highlights>
        <highlights>Man City could have cut Chelsea's advantage to one point atop EPL table</highlights>
        <highlights>Elsewhere, Manchester United and Tottenham played to a goalless draw</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-28T20:55:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Sunday's action in football's Premier League failed to match the Boxing Day goal-fest but that didn't mean there was a shortage of drama.Most of it took place in Manchester, with surging defending champion Manchester City coming unstuck against relegation threatened Burnley.Cruising with a 2-0 lead after 35 minutes, City relinquished two goals in the second half to only settle for a point. Out went its nine-match winning streak.The second-half lapse meant City failed to close the gap to one point on leader Chelsea, which had earlier drawn 10-man Southampton 1-1. The margin remains three points.Manuel Pellegrini's men -- despite missing strikers Sergio Aguero and Edin Dzeko -- netted six goals in their last two matches and when the in-form David Silva and holding midfielder Fernandinho found the back of the net within 33 minutes, it appeared as if a landslide win was on the cards.But City relaxed and plucky Burnley -- which has improved in the past two months -- pounced.George Boyd began the comeback in the 47th minute before Ashley Barnes leveled past Joe Hart in the 81st."It was a big opportunity to get two more points," Pellegrini was quoted as saying by the BBC. "Everybody would think the game was over but I always say it is never over until the last minute."The pitch was very heavy, two games in 48 hours, but we were winning 2-0. Once it was 2-2 we didn't have the legs to score. We only had two shots after that."We didn't play well in the second half."Chelsea boss Jose Mourinho was left bewildered with the officiating at Southampton, feeling his team should have been awarded a penalty when Cesc Fabregas hit the ground under a challenge from Matt Targett early in the second half with the score tied 1-1.No penalty was given and Fabregas was booked by Anthony Taylor.In recent weeks, allegations of diving have centered around Chelsea players Gary Cahill, Diego Costa, Willian and Branislav Ivanovic."I can't believe that the referee didn't give a penalty," Mourinho told Sky. "I can believe that Southampton defended with everything they have -- good organization, good spirit, good solidarity between the players."I can also understand the game that my players played. They tried to win, especially in the second half, when we had complete control. I cannot understand such a big penalty (decision). Or I understand (it could be) a consequence of something that looks like a campaign."Out of nothing, (West Ham manager) Sam Allardyce starts speaking about Chelsea players diving, and in another game it is another coach."Chelsea bossed possession with 60% of the ball but managed one shot on target, Eden Hazard's clinical finish in first-half injury time. Morgan Schneiderlin was sent off for the fourth-place Saints in the 88th minute, tripping Fabregas for a second yellow.Manchester United manager Louis van Gaal was not happy, either, unimpressed with teams having to play two games in three days. Such, however, is life over the festive period in England.After United and Tottenham played to a 0-0 draw in London, he described the football as ugly."The second half was a struggle," the Dutchman told BT Sport. "You can see the players can't recover in two days. It was an ugly match."But United would have scored two or three goals in the first half if not for the heroics of Tottenham keeper Hugo Lloris.Elsewhere, Arsenal rose into a tie on points with Southampton after beating West Ham 2-1 on the road; Stoke heaped more pressure on Alan Irvine by topping West Bromwich Albion 2-0; and draw specialist Sunderland couldn't register a winner against Aston Villa even though it played most of the second half with an extra man. Their match concluded 0-0.Hull must have thought its troubles were over when it beat Sunderland two days ago, but Steve Bruce's Tigers fell at home 1-0 to last-place Leicester -- which had lost six straight.Crystal Palace, which sacked Neil Warnock on Saturday, claimed a point after holding QPR to a 0-0 result. QPR -- owned by Air Asia's Tony Fernandes -- held a 5-2-2 record at home while losing all nine of its road games.In the late kickoff, roller-coaster Newcastle beat Everton 3-2 at home to hand the Toffees a sixth loss in their last eight.Struggling Liverpool hosts Swansea on Monday.No more EPL for TorresMourinho and Chelsea will no longer be calling upon Fernando Torres.Chelsea announced late Saturday that the Spanish striker -- an $80 million flop for the Blues -- would be moving to AC Milan permanently following his loan move to the Italian giant.Torres scored only 20 goals in 110 league appearances for Chelsea in three years, although he won the Champions League during that time. It followed a prolific spell in front of goal with Liverpool."Chelsea Football Club thanks Fernando for his service during the past four seasons and wishes him the very best for the future," a Chelsea statement said.Torres, according to reports, could be headed back to Atletico Madrid in another loan move. The World Cup winner first made a name for himself at the Spanish club.Read: Chelsea upends West Ham</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228133231-barnes-burnley-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228113431-silva-tease-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228133542-mourinho-frustration-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228134007-hazard-goal-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228134253-lloris-save-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228133231-barnes-burnley-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228113431-silva-tease-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228133542-mourinho-frustration-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228134007-hazard-goal-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228134253-lloris-save-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141211130157-intv-baldesarra-klinsmann-part-1-00040418-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140227134607-intv-davies-bayern-munich-stein-of-secrets-00005923-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140715071412-german-fans-celebrate-world-cup-victory-story-body.png</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140713005032-germanys-football-resurgance-00003409-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140707194809-pkg-sweeney-germany-football-superfan-00002613-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140629104435-newday-american-soccer-german-influence-00031725-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216100552-henry-new-york-laughing-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605114319-eibar-gal-9-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017152545-gallery-real-madrid-refurb-6-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141027022422-bpr-south-african-soccor-senzo-meyiwa-death-00000402-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020180630-roma-centurion-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020132745-kreshnik-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017150734-ched-evans-smiling-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016105457-lionel-messi-opener-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122943-inter-milan-fan-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013170740-martin-odegaard-norway-debut-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010121745-indian-football-league-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002124314-davies-intv-rio-ferdinand-racism-00002712-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192812im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908152849-odegaard-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1437322">
        <title>Supermodel's supermaxi can't catch Wild Oats in Sydney-Hobart boat race</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/28/sport/yachting-sydney-hobart-wild-oats/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Wild Oats XI achieves a record eighth line honor in the annual Rolex Sydney-Hobart boat race</highlights>
        <highlights>Wild Oats XI finishes in two days, two hours, three minutes and 26 seconds</highlights>
        <highlights>Comanche placed second after entering the race with much fanfare and making a fast start</highlights>
        <highlights>Comanche is owned by Netscape co-founder Jim Clark and his model wife</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-28T14:22:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- The supermodel's new super yacht couldn't quite keep up with an established vessel in the annual Rolex Sydney-Hobart race.Comanche -- owned by Netscape co-founder Jim Clark and his wife, Australian model Kristy Hinze-Clark -- had to settle for second behind history maker Wild Oats XI in the 70th running of the 'Bluewater Classic.'Wild Oats XI became the first boat to achieve eight line honors, surpassing the seven line honors of Morna -- later called Kurrewa IV -- in the 1950s and 60s when it crossed the finish line in two days, two hours, three minutes and 26 seconds Sunday.Comanche had been closing the gap in the 628-nautical mile race but ultimately was 49 minutes slower than Wild Oats XI, which is owned by wine magnate Robert Oatley."To rewrite a bit of sailing history doesn't come along every day," Wild Oats XI's skipper, Mark Richards, was quoted as saying by the race's official website. "To win a Hobart is a great honor but to win an eighth, I can't believe I am here."Comanche was unbelievably impressive down Sydney Harbour and the whole first night she had the legs on us. We thought, 'How are we going to handle this thing?'"It was definitely our toughest race -- to have a boat so close for so much of the race, especially when she's faster than you. I said to the guys 'We've got to hang in there, hang tough, minimize our losses and wait for the first opportunity we get to attack.'"That opportunity came in the Bass Strait.The lighter conditions suited Wild Oats XI, which opened up a big lead."We were about a quarter of the way into Bass Strait and expecting a westerly breeze, and all of a sudden Stan (navigator Stan Honey) came up from down below and said, 'I just got a new weather file, this is not looking good,'" Comanche skipper Ken Read was quoted as saying by the race's official website."We were two miles ahead of them, in bumpy seas, and they literally went by us, probably going a knot or two faster at the time, and they just sailed into more pressure and just kept extending on the whole fleet."Both boats sailed a flawless race but they had their day. They had 12 hours where they had Wild Oats' weather, but that's racing."While it wasn't known whether Comanche would return next year, Oatley said Wild Oats XI would be back."We will be back next year, yes, we'll definitely be back next year," Oatley was quoted as saying by the race's website. "She is the best boat in the world. She's proved that."Read: Comanche's fast start</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228090143-wild-oats-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226160220-comanche1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161027-comanche2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161217-comanche3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161528-comanche4-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161956-comanche5-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228090143-wild-oats-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226160220-comanche1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161027-comanche2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161217-comanche3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161528-comanche4-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226161956-comanche5-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130110042529-mainsail-sydney-hobart-race-rio-2016-c-00053323-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130110114639-mainsail-sydney-hobart-race-rio-2016-b-00014322-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141211140112-spc-mainsail-route-du-rhum-c-00011816-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141109170058-sailing-drones-11-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141021113508-glass-superyacht-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020114317-hms-endeavour-on-sea-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140922125049-team-alvimedica-duo-on-board-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140918112839-triton-submarine-ocean-floor-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140815111129-landsailing-tip-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140729160336-superyacht-hotel-london-exterior-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140312105901-alex-thomson-running-up-mast-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140707104145-endeavour-elizabeth-meyer-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140710151054-rolls-royce-unmanned-cargo-ships-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140710140655-henley-fans-on-boat-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605110126-sailing-china-sail-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140611102858-kate-middleton-americas-cup-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140530183634-superyacht-eyos-expeditions-ice-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192814im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140513082831-turner-burial-at-sea-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1438551">
        <title>Another U.S. downhill winner in Italy</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/28/sport/ganong-downhill-win-italy/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Travis Ganong wins his first downhill by claiming top spot in Santa Catarina</highlights>
        <highlights>In a shortened run, he beat Austria's Matthias Mayer by 0.09 seconds</highlights>
        <highlights>It was the U.S.'s second downhill triumph in Italy in about a week</highlights>
        <highlights>Sweden's Sara Hector also won her first race in a women's giant slalom</highlights>
        <date>2014-12-28T16:01:00.000Z</date>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- The way things have gone for the U.S. men in downhills in Italy this month, they probably wish every race could be held there.After Steven Nyman won one of skiing's classics in Val Gardena about a week ago, Travis Ganong claimed the opening victory of his career by bettering the field in Santa Catarina -- a venue long known on the women's circuit but making its debut among the men.The course shortened due to high winds and bad visibility, Ganong took advantage and won in a time of one minute, 32.42 seconds.He was 0.09 seconds faster than Austria's Matthias Mayer and 0.21 seconds faster than home favorite Dominik Paris."It was a perfect run," Ganong told the U.S. ski team's website. "I love to take on a new challenge and a new slope. I love the hill -- the mountains are huge here and it's fun skiing."I went really, really straight in a couple areas. It was really smooth and I was able to carry it all the way down. The last big carousel turn I did perfectly -- I don't think I could do that again if I tried."Hopefully this will keep going all year. My New Year's resolution is to do this more often."Nyman finished 15th, two spots better than Kjetil Jansrud of Norway. Jansrud, though, maintained his lead in both the downhill and overall standings.First win for Hector, tooGanong wasn't the lone racer to capture a maiden victory Sunday, as Sweden's Sara Hector triumphed in a women's giant slalom in Kuhtai in Tirol, Austria -- new to the World Cup tour.In second heading into the final run behind American Mikaela Shiffrin, Hector attacked the course and made up the 0.27-second deficit.Austria's Anna Fenninger moved up to second, with Shiffrin -- whose specialty is the slalom -- dropping to third."It's not easy to put words on such emotions right now," Hector was quoted as saying by the FIS website. "To be on top of the podium is so special."Fenninger solidified her spot in second in the overall standings behind Tina Maze -- who tied for seventh Sunday.Fenninger is also second in the giant slalom standings, trailing compatriot Eva-Maria Brem.A lack of snow in Semmering, Austria, prompted the move to Kuhtai in Tirol.Read: Vonn misses out on record</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141228095929-ganong-italy-downhill-story-top.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141224141053-spc-alpine-edge-family-affair-00014206-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141215114414-spc-alpine-edge-anja-paerson-00013810-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141215112453-spc-alpine-edge-henrik-kristoffersen-00025603-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141215112453-spc-alpine-edge-henrik-kristoffersen-00025603-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140314165916-vonn-crystal-globe-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140324180548-spc-alpine-edge-world-cup-winners-00004805-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140324182227-spc-alpine-edge-world-cup-crystal-globe-00010313-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131029141104-blurred-runners-vertical-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140129184450-spc-alpine-edge-kitzbuhel-ski-race-history-00001929-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140129184426-spc-alpine-edge-ski-boot-technology-00002512-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131225114329-void-view-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131216110406-spc-apline-edge-ski-safety-val-d-isere-00001901-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131216111244-spc-apline-edge-giant-slalom-masterclass-00011004-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131213154910-spc-alpine-edge-ski-gadgets-00015430-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131202164350-spc-alpine-edge-mikaela-shiffrin-00004521-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192816im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131202164905-spc-alpine-edge-raptor-ski-course-00031025-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1439781">
        <title>Cricket Australia trademarks '63 not out' after death of its star Phillip Hughes</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/27/sport/cricket-hughes-63-not-out-smith/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Cricket Australia trademarks term "63 not out"</highlights>
        <highlights>Score reached by Phillip Hughes in his final innings</highlights>
        <highlights>Governing body says it is to prevent people cashing in</highlights>
        <highlights>Australia in strong position in third Test against India</highlights>
        <author>By Paul Gittings, CNN</author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Cricket Australia has trademarked the term "63 not out" in an attempt to prevent people cashing in on the death of its Test batsman Phillip Hughes.The 25-year-old Hughes died after being hit on the head by a ball in a domestic match in Sydney last month.He had reached the score of 63 runs when the tragic accident occurred.Read: Australia cricketer Hughes dies after freak accidentHis untimely death stunned the sporting world and the scheduled first Test between Australia and India in Adelaide had to be postponed as his teammates struggled to cope with their grief at his passing.#63notout is now a milestone of remembrance and tribute for Aussie batsmen. Story &amp; video: http://t.co/BHgbzxPbzR pic.twitter.com/7az2f2EnUFTributes on social media initially centered around a campaign #putyourbatsout on Twitter as thousands of people photographed cricket bats in unusual places to mark their respect for Hughes.But 63 not out also became an iconic symbol of the batsman's life and when the first Test eventually took place, spectators were asked to stand for 63 seconds of applause before the start.Australian players reaching that score during their innings also marked its significance with gestures and many in the crowd wore T-shirts or held up signs with 63 not out featured.Read: Clarke leads tributes at funeral of cricketer HughesHowever, cricket authorities in Australia and Hughes' representatives have become concerned about the volume of unlicensed memorabilia, mostly clothing and stickers, and the use of online auction sites to promote the various offerings.Cricket Australia said the agreement was purely "defensive" to prevent others trying to exploit Hughes' memory."CA registered the trademark in conjunction with Phillip's management to prevent others trying to exploit Phillip's memory," a spokesperson told CNN."There was some evidence of that starting," it added.The entire Australia-India series has been played out with continuous reminders of Hughes. The Australian team is wearing shirts with the number 408 stitched in.Hughes was the 408th player to represent his country in Test matches, the highest level of international cricket.Australia's players, especially those closest to Hughes, have also produced inspired performances against India, taking a 2-0 lead and dominating the Third Test which started on Boxing Day in Melbourne.Read: Captain's knock from Smith at MCGStand-in captain Steve Smith reached his Test-best 192 on Saturday as the home team posted a formidable first innings of 530.He was supported by innings from Brad Haddin (55), Mitchell Johnson (28) and Ryan Harris (74) as Australia scored quickly against the Indian bowling attack.India fought back to reach 108 for one wicket by the close, but its chancing of winning the match and attempting to square the four-match series is effectively over.Read: Is cricket safe?</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203125504-phil-hughes-funeral-michael-clarke-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203124041-phil-hughes-funeral-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102818-phil-hughes-funeral-4-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102516-phil-hughes-funeral-3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203101932-phil-hughes-funeral-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203101842-phil-hughes-funeral-1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102037-phil-hughes-memory-1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102955-phil-hughes-memory-3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102303-phil-hughes-memory-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126000140-phil-hughes-file-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210230-gallery-phil-hughes-two-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210234-gallery-phil-hughes-three-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210241-gallery-phil-hughes-six-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203125504-phil-hughes-funeral-michael-clarke-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203124041-phil-hughes-funeral-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102818-phil-hughes-funeral-4-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102516-phil-hughes-funeral-3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203101932-phil-hughes-funeral-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203101842-phil-hughes-funeral-1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102037-phil-hughes-memory-1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102955-phil-hughes-memory-3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203102303-phil-hughes-memory-2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126000140-phil-hughes-file-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210230-gallery-phil-hughes-two-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210234-gallery-phil-hughes-three-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126210241-gallery-phil-hughes-six-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141126000140-phil-hughes-file-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141125025553-phil-hughes-on-ground-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141127000942-dnt-snell-phillip-hughes-australian-cricketer-death-00002521-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141203125410-sot-michael-clarke-eulogy-phillip-hughes-funeral-00001402-story-body.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141117183610-36-what-a-shot-1118-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140728161451-french-8-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140727115456-steve-way-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140725011651-queen-selfie-commonwealth-games-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140725202155-rowsell-gold-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723205917-barrowman-glasgow-kiss-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140507120659-jackson-fulham-statue-close-up-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140507132942-helena-costa-2-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140425171545-dan-carter-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140403104700-bali-bombing-2002-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140304171052-cnnphotos-muhammad-ali-02-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140223114948-01-visions-sochi-0223-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192818im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/131210154043-babette-march-sports-illustrated-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
    <news newsid="1441625">
        <title>The joke is on West Ham as Chelsea keeps up pace at the top of EPL</title>
        <url>/web/20150102180736/http://edition.cnn.com/2014/12/26/sport/football/football-chelsea-west-ham-mourinho/index.html?hpt=isp_c2</url>
        <highlights>Chelsea beats West Ham 2-0 in English Premier League</highlights>
        <highlights>Goals from John Terry and Diego Costa</highlights>
        <highlights>Champions Manchester City keep pace at top with 3-1 win at WBA</highlights>
        <highlights>NEW: Crystal Palace sacks boss Neil Warnock after 3-1 defeat to Southampton</highlights>
        <author></author>
        <content>Follow us at @WorldSportCNN and like us on Facebook(CNN) -- Jose Mourinho's Chelsea had the last laugh on London rival West Ham to keep up its relentless pace at the top of the English Premier League with a 2-0 Boxing Day home win.The pre-match build up had centered on Mourinho's remarks after the corresponding fixture last season -- when peeved by the West Ham defensive tactics in a 0-0 draw -- he said manager Sam Allardyce and the team had been playing "football from the 19th century" -- amid other sharp criticism.PIC: The West Ham United team coach (and horse) has arrived at @chelseafc for today's game #19thcenturyfootball pic.twitter.com/qC9FbEvsQXMourinho backtracked on these remarks and has paid compliment to West Ham's fine form in the current campaign, in fourth place ahead of the latest round of games, but it did not prevent the Hammers' official Twitter feed from posting a witty rejoinder before the match.It featured a tweet with a sepia-colored picture of a horse and cart, accompanied by the caption: "The West Ham United team coach (and horse) has arrived at @chelseafc for today's game #19thcenturyfootball".In truth, once the match got underway there was little the visitors could do to stem the tide of almost constant Chelsea attacks, with very little in reply.Eden Hazard, recovered from the knock he received in the 2-0 win over Stoke Monday, was a strong influence again for the Blues, who went ahead when John Terry reacted quickly to a Diego Costa header from a Cesc Fabregas's corner.It was the former England international's second goal in two games and his team might have been further ahead but for Adrian producing a fine save from Nemanja Matic and top scorer Costa shooting over.Hazard was nearly on the score sheet early in the second half, but it was the Belgian international who turned provider as he played Costa through to finish clinically for this 13th of the season just after the hour mark.Further goals might have followed with the table toppers in confident mood, although West Ham came close to cutting the deficit when substitute Morgan Amalfitano hit the post with a shot."We played a very good game against a very difficult opponent. When we scored, we had the game always under control," Mourinho told Sky Sports. "I am really happy. We are doing very well."Later, defending champions Manchester City kept the gap on Chelsea to three points with a fine 3-1 win at West Bromwich Albion, while third-placed Manchester United eased past Newcastle 3-1, with Wayne Rooney scoring twice.Southampton won 3-1 at Crystal Palace to leapfrog West Ham into fourth spot, the defeat the last match in charge for home boss Neil Warnock.He was sacked by the south London club Sunday with Keith Millen coming in as caretaker boss.Tottenham Hotspur took closer order to the Champions League spots with a 2-1 win at bottom club Leicester.In the Boxing Day late game, Alexis Sanchez saw his penalty saved by Rob Green then put Arsenal ahead in a 2-1 win over QPR at the Emirates.The Gunners had Olivier Giroud sent off for a headbutt on Nedum Onuoha, but added a second through Tomas Rosicky. A Charlie Austin penalty reduced the deficit but the 10-man home side hung on as Arsenal went sixth.</content>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226152048-diego-costa-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175050-epl1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175253-epl2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226192247-epl4-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175549-epl3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226152048-diego-costa-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175050-epl1-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175253-epl2-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226192247-epl4-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141226175549-epl3-topics.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141216100552-henry-new-york-laughing-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140605114319-eibar-gal-9-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017152545-gallery-real-madrid-refurb-6-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141027022422-bpr-south-african-soccor-senzo-meyiwa-death-00000402-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020180630-roma-centurion-tease-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141020132745-kreshnik-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016173841-balotelli-tease-1-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017150734-ched-evans-smiling-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016105457-lionel-messi-opener-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122943-inter-milan-fan-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141013170740-martin-odegaard-norway-debut-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141010121745-indian-football-league-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002124314-davies-intv-rio-ferdinand-racism-00002712-video-tease.jpg</photos>
        <photos>http://web.archive.org/web/20150102192819im_/http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140908152849-odegaard-celebrates-video-tease.jpg</photos>
    </news>
</ns2:topic>
